Speaker 0: You see that?
Speaker 0: They're throwing shit up there.
Speaker 0: Right down there?
Speaker 0: Yeah, right.
Speaker 0: Not for nothing.
Speaker 0: I'm not a fan of him just leaving five of us down there.
Speaker 0: We should all be fucking together up there.
Speaker 0: It's not.
Speaker 0: We should all be together up there and that's it.
Speaker 0: Well, I just said to fucking McDonough, like, the fact that they just leave five of us here, like, we should be up there with everybody else.
Speaker 0: You know what I'm saying?
Speaker 0: Yeah, but that last car is coming down here.
Speaker 0: I don't want to go straight the fuck here.
Speaker 0: Yeah, I know.
Speaker 0: No.
Speaker 0: Huh?
Speaker 0: Fucking fuck it.
Speaker 0: Look at all the bottles.
Speaker 0: they're hucking at them down there.
Speaker 0: Let's go down there, Pat.
Speaker 0: Fuck this.
Speaker 0: Hey, what up, bro, man?
Speaker 0: What a fucking mess.
Speaker 0: Bro, bro!
Speaker 0: Rap God.
Speaker 0: Bro, bro.
Speaker 0: If you guys don't have families, or, like, brothers and sisters, like, you know, like, you know.
Speaker 0: Fuck, who the fuck gassed?
Speaker 0: That's fucking Tia Gassed, that's what I fucking want to see.
Speaker 0: Fuck!
Speaker 0: I have no fucking idea.
Speaker 0: I can't fucking see.
Speaker 0: I want this left open to dump out any shitheads or to pull in anybody we need.
Speaker 0: Dope, right there.
Speaker 0: Fucking hell.
Speaker 0: Did you get that gas in your ass?
Speaker 0: We're just spraying and keep moving.
Speaker 0: Keep spraying, keep moving, that's what we need to do.
Speaker 0: If he lost us we gotta just keep fucking getting on.
Speaker 0: You're fucking absolutely.
Speaker 0: This guy's crazy because I'm not in a cruiser, we can fucking go.
Speaker 0: Get the cruiser!
Speaker 0: Get the fuck away.
Speaker 0: Stay back.
Speaker 0: Get her out of here.
Speaker 0: Back up, back up, back up.
Speaker 0: Back up, back up.
Speaker 0: Hold it here, hold it here.
Speaker 0: Hold it here.
Speaker 0: You're fucking out of here.
Speaker 0: You're gonna see that.
Speaker 0: Take that shit out.
Speaker 0: Don't blame me.
Speaker 0: We don't gotta touch her.
Speaker 0: Don't touch her.
Speaker 0: It's not everybody.
Speaker 0: Don't touch us.
Speaker 0: You guys over here on the side.
Speaker 0: Don't touch us, don't touch us.
Speaker 0: Don't touch us.
Speaker 0: Don't touch me.
Speaker 0: Move back, move back.
Speaker 0: No, no, no, no, no, no.
Speaker 0: No, no, no, no, no.
Speaker 0: No, no, no, no.
Speaker 0: Please.
Speaker 0: Come on, man.
Speaker 0: Black man, I could be your child.
Speaker 0: I don't need you here.
Speaker 0: Please, please.
Speaker 0: They would kill you too.
Speaker 0: Take your uniform off.
Speaker 0: Move forward, move forward.
Speaker 0: Why can't we stand here?
Speaker 0: It's our possibility.
Speaker 0: Why do we gotta move?
Speaker 0: Is that your new whip?
Speaker 0: You wanna whoop me with that?
Speaker 0: Why do we gotta move?
Speaker 0: Huh?
Speaker 0: Hey guys, let's get over here.
Speaker 0: There's a bunch of people coming in from behind us.
Speaker 0: In fact, where's the other guys?
Speaker 0: Dudley, Kato, and James are.
Speaker 0: They might still be back on Winter Street.
Speaker 0: Where's James?
Speaker 0: Trooper, we're sitting ducks out in the middle of the fucking street like this.
Speaker 0: You aren't gonna go back that way.
Speaker 0: I gotta get this car out of here.
Speaker 0: He's got a baby in the car.
Speaker 0: I want him out of here.
Speaker 0: Come on.
Speaker 0: Let this guy out of here.
Speaker 0: He's got a baby in the car.
Speaker 0: I want to get him out of here.
Speaker 0: Deputy, he's got a baby in the car.
Speaker 0: I want to get him out.
Speaker 0: He's got a baby in the car.
Speaker 0: -He's coughing.
Speaker 0: -He's a fucking idiot.
Speaker 0: -Go ahead.
Speaker 0: Just keep going nice and slow.
Speaker 0: -All right.
Speaker 0: -I got hit by a rock.
Speaker 0: -Out of here.
Speaker 0: He's got a baby in the car.
Speaker 0: Put your lights on.
Speaker 0: Try to get him out of here.
Speaker 0: He's got a kid in the car.
Speaker 0: I'm trying to fuck him.
Speaker 0: Listen, you stay right behind her.
Speaker 0: She's going to try to get you out of here, all right?
Speaker 0: You stay right behind her.
Speaker 0: Where the fuck she went?
Speaker 0: They stayed back.
Speaker 0: Told them to fucking stay behind you.
Speaker 0: Why don't you do what you can, Andy?
Speaker 0: Fuck it.
Speaker 0: -What's up?
Speaker 0: -Just watch yourself.
Speaker 0: -Thank you.
Speaker 0: -You shoot me in the face, you can't go one-on-one.
Speaker 0: -And get out of here.
Speaker 0: -You can fucking stay.
Speaker 0: Here you go.
Speaker 0: One-on-one.
Speaker 0: Talk.
Speaker 0: Let's go.
Speaker 0: -I just hit my bottle.
Speaker 0: -I'm fucking scared.
Speaker 0: I'm scared.
Speaker 0: -No shit.
Speaker 0: I'm just here.
Speaker 0: I'm coming from behind us too now.
Speaker 0: We're sitting ducks over here like this.
Speaker 0: It's fucking nuts.
Speaker 0: We're sitting ducks like this in the fucking middle.
Speaker 0: -What the fuck am I asking, man?
Speaker 0: What the fuck?
Speaker 0: -We need to get the fuck out of here.
Speaker 0: What are we doing now?
Speaker 0: We're fucking sitting ducks like this.
Speaker 0: They're behind us in front of us.
Speaker 0: -We need help at the Beach House Hall.
Speaker 0: Beach House Hall.
Speaker 0: -Be advised, if you do not disperse--.
Speaker 0: -I'm going fucking hard to tell them who's the fuck.
Speaker 0: -Be advised.
Speaker 0: You are hereby ordered by the state police to disperse or we will deploy the gas.
Speaker 0: -What's that?
Speaker 0: -They're going to deploy your sheet.
Speaker 0: We're going to move.
Speaker 0: [INAUDIBLE].
Speaker 0: -All right?
Speaker 0: -Stay tight.
Speaker 0: -I am causing a traffic jam in the middle of an intersection.
Speaker 0: What are you doing?
Speaker 0: -They might have been right or left.
Speaker 0: -Hold the line.
Speaker 0: Hold the line.
Speaker 0: Go.
Speaker 0: Come on, get off.
Speaker 0: Get off and go.
Speaker 0: Go.
Speaker 0: -They were leaving.
Speaker 0: That's why they're out on the park.
Speaker 0: Now you're moving them back to the park?
Speaker 0: They're fucking kids.
Speaker 0: The neighborhoods gave them love all day long.
Speaker 0: You know who did it?
Speaker 0: These are fucking kids, man.
Speaker 0: Look at them.
Speaker 0: -Go somewhere you aren't.
Speaker 0: -They were leaving.
Speaker 0: That's why they're out on the park.
Speaker 0: -Hold that.
Speaker 0: -Be advised.
Speaker 0: We're seeing you.
Speaker 0: Be advised.
Speaker 0: -I can't breathe.
Speaker 0: -Idiots.
Speaker 0: -Take some knees and we go home.
Speaker 0: -Take a knee.
Speaker 0: Take a knee.
Speaker 0: Hold just one.
Speaker 0: I'm scared of you at all.
Speaker 0: -Who do you serve?
Speaker 0: Who do you serve?
Speaker 0: Look up the street.
Speaker 0: Do you have kids?
Speaker 0: -You have kids?
Speaker 0: -Please move up the street, please.
Speaker 0: Please move up the street.
Speaker 0: Take a fucking knee right now!
Speaker 0: Why don't you take a fucking knee?
Speaker 0: Which one of you has a fucking heart?
Speaker 0: Which one of you has natural?
Speaker 0: Operator, this is a fight.
Speaker 0: That's the most important thing, let's not kill them.
Speaker 0: Portestants!
Speaker 0: We are here!
Speaker 0: I know, I live... Is the train open?
Speaker 0: It didn't fucking work!
Speaker 0: [INAUDIBLE].
Speaker 0: -What do they say?
Speaker 0: -Everyone on three miles, donning gas masks.
Speaker 0: -Why don't you do that?
Speaker 0: -Oh, fuck off.
Speaker 0: [INTERPOSING VOICES].
Speaker 0: -Don't hit me.
Speaker 0: Don't hit me.
Speaker 0: [INTERPOSING VOICES].
Speaker 0: [INTERPOSING VOICES] -Go down that way.
Speaker 0: Go that way.
Speaker 0: [INTERPOSING VOICES] -I don't know what the fuck that is.
Speaker 0: It's like I fucking fist milk.
Speaker 0: What if it's fucking milk all fucking paint?
Speaker 0: [INTERPOSING VOICES].
Speaker 0: [INTERPOSING VOICES] -I think they're going down to that Wash and Essex.
Speaker 0: They're looking at the house now, man.
Speaker 0: -Quench him in your fucking mouth.
Speaker 0: Quench him in your fucking mouth.
Speaker 0: Shit.
Speaker 0: Gas coming down this way, guys.
Speaker 0: If you get gas masks, give it to Donald.
Speaker 0: [INAUDIBLE].
Speaker 0: -You don't have your mouth?
Speaker 0: -Any word where Pat went?
Speaker 0: -No.
Speaker 0: He texted me if I was OK.
Speaker 0: I'm just going to let him know that I'm with you.
Speaker 0: So I don't know.
Speaker 0: He said that we just got lost.
Speaker 0: He was OK.
Speaker 0: -I think they kept going when they were going on camera.
Speaker 0: -What's that?
Speaker 0: -My car's fucked.
Speaker 0: -Is there a tango bolt?
Speaker 0: -Yep.
Speaker 0: -I'm not able to back up, and I don't know if I'm going to--.
Speaker 0: -Quench him in all the carness right now.
Speaker 0: He's trying to move this crap.
Speaker 0: Oil kit 23-1, do you need a boat?
Speaker 0: -What do you have on fire?
Speaker 0: -Wally, did you hear that?
Speaker 0: You know what's on fire at Wash and Essex?
Speaker 0: What's on fire at Wash and Essex?
Speaker 0: -That way.
Speaker 0: You'll be all right.
Speaker 0: -Wait, can I go that way?
Speaker 0: Don't pepper spray me.
Speaker 0: Can I go that way?
Speaker 0: -No.
Speaker 0: -'Cause y'all be pepper spraying and shit, and I'm not trying to get out of here.
Speaker 0: -Is he going to let him go?
Speaker 0: -Yeah.
Speaker 0: -He'll build the bikes.
Speaker 0: -Yeah, all right.
Speaker 0: [POLICE RADIO CHATTER] -Huh?
Speaker 0: You stay here the whole time?
Speaker 0: -It's a little late in the video.