Speaker 0: [BEEPING].
Speaker 0: -You see that?
Speaker 0: They're throwing shit up there.
Speaker 0: -Right down there?
Speaker 0: [POLICE RADIO CHATTER] -We're fucking this way.
Speaker 0: -Yeah, right.
Speaker 0: -Not for nothing, I'm not a fan of him just leaving fucking five of us down there.
Speaker 0: We should all be fucking together up there.
Speaker 0: -It's not.
Speaker 0: -No, we should all be together up there, and that's it.
Speaker 0: -Well, I just said to fucking McDonald, like, the fact that they just leave five of us here, like, we should be up there with everybody else.
Speaker 0: You know what I'm saying?
Speaker 0: -Yeah, I know.
Speaker 0: -Huck and fuck it, look at all the bottles.
Speaker 0: they're hucking at him down there.
Speaker 0: [POLICE RADIO CHATTER] -Let's go down there, Pat.
Speaker 0: Fuck this.
Speaker 0: [POLICE RADIO CHATTER] -Hey, what up, bro, man?
Speaker 0: What a fucking mess.
Speaker 0: -This way.
Speaker 0: [POLICE RADIO CHATTER] -Come on down here, man.
Speaker 0: [POLICE RADIO CHATTER] -Lock up.
Speaker 0: [POLICE RADIO CHATTER] -This is middle.
Speaker 0: [POLICE RADIO CHATTER] -All right.
Speaker 0: Hold up.
Speaker 0: [POLICE RADIO CHATTER] -Hold up on the street.
Speaker 0: [POLICE RADIO CHATTER] -You guys don't have families?
Speaker 0: Or like brothers and sisters?
Speaker 0: Like, you don't--.
Speaker 0: like, you don't--.
Speaker 0: -Excuse me.
Speaker 0: (indistinct chatter) - What gas do you have?
Speaker 0: You gas this fucking place?
Speaker 0: Fuck.
Speaker 0: Ah, fuck.
Speaker 0: Who the fuck gassed?
Speaker 0: - That's fucking tear gas.
Speaker 0: That's what the fucking was saying.
Speaker 0: - Fuck.
Speaker 0: Huh?
Speaker 0: I have no fucking idea.
Speaker 0: (coughing) I can't fucking see, are you fucking kidding me?
Speaker 0: I need a pop down here.
Speaker 0: - I want this left open to dump out any shitheads or to pull in anybody we need.
Speaker 0: Dope, right there, just over your ass.
Speaker 0: - Fucking nuts.
Speaker 0: Did you get that gas in your ass?
Speaker 0: You just start spraying and keep moving.
Speaker 0: Keep spraying, keep moving.
Speaker 0: That's what we need to do.
Speaker 0: He lost us, we gotta just keep fucking getting on him.
Speaker 0: This guy's crazy for coming out in a T-shirt.
Speaker 0: Where do you think you're going?
Speaker 0: - Get the cruiser.
Speaker 0: Stay back.
Speaker 0: Get around here.
Speaker 0: Grab this and get around here.
Speaker 0: Hey, stop.
Speaker 0: Back up.
Speaker 0: - Back, back, everybody back up.
Speaker 0: - Hey, hold him, hold him.
Speaker 0: - Hold him.
Speaker 0: Hold it in, hold it in.
Speaker 0: Hold it in.
Speaker 0: Hold him.
Speaker 0: - Right there.
Speaker 0: - All right, get the fuck out of here.
Speaker 0: You ain't gonna see nothing.
Speaker 0: I don't want anything to do with you.
Speaker 0: - Take that shit down.
Speaker 0: - Don't blame me, because who the fuck is he?
Speaker 0: - Calm down, we don't gotta touch him.
Speaker 0: Don't touch him.
Speaker 0: - Don't touch him.
Speaker 0: - He's got families.
Speaker 0: - He's got everybody.
Speaker 0: - He's got you locked.
Speaker 0: - He's got families too, that's all.
Speaker 0: - This guy's over here on the side.
Speaker 0: - Don't touch us.
Speaker 0: Don't touch us.
Speaker 0: - You gotta move back.
Speaker 0: Please don't touch my stick.
Speaker 0: Get your hands off my stick.
Speaker 0: - You gotta move back.
Speaker 0: You gotta move back.
Speaker 0: Move back.
Speaker 0: - No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Speaker 0: - Please, please.
Speaker 0: Please.
Speaker 0: - Come on, man.
Speaker 0: - Don't do what?
Speaker 0: - Black man, I could be a child.
Speaker 0: I don't need to be a child.
Speaker 0: - Back up.
Speaker 0: - Don't do that.
Speaker 0: Don't let him do that.
Speaker 0: - Take your phone.
Speaker 0: - Don't let him do that.
Speaker 0: - Please.
Speaker 0: - That's why we're here.
Speaker 0: - They would kill you too, if you take that uniform off.
Speaker 0: You are just like him.
Speaker 0: - All right, move forward.
Speaker 0: Move.
Speaker 0: - You move forward?
Speaker 0: - Hey, you guys gotta move.
Speaker 0: - Why can't we stand here?
Speaker 0: We can protest.
Speaker 0: - It's our first amendment right.
Speaker 0: Why do we gotta move?
Speaker 0: - Just move back.
Speaker 0: - Why do we gotta move?
Speaker 0: It's our right to move and protest.
Speaker 0: - But why?
Speaker 0: Why?
Speaker 0: - Y'all can go around us.
Speaker 0: - It's our right to be here.
Speaker 0: - It's your peace.
Speaker 0: - We've been peaceful until you got here.
Speaker 0: - So I'm supposed to be here?
Speaker 0: - We've been peaceful this whole time.
Speaker 0: - No, that just makes the girl.
Speaker 0: - What?
Speaker 0: - You're the only one.
Speaker 0: - I can't protest here.
Speaker 0: I'm surrounded.
Speaker 0: - Yeah, this is a public street.
Speaker 0: Like, why can't we protest?
Speaker 0: Why can't we protest?
Speaker 0: It's our first amendment right.
Speaker 0: Why do we not get the same right as you?
Speaker 0: Why do we gotta move?
Speaker 0: - For what?
Speaker 0: For what?
Speaker 0: This is a public street.
Speaker 0: - I want a peaceful protest here.
Speaker 0: - Like, why do we gotta move?
Speaker 0: Like, everybody else forgot to refer to us.
Speaker 0: No, no, you have to move back.
Speaker 0: - Move back, please.
Speaker 0: - Get off of me.
Speaker 0: Get off of me.
Speaker 0: - You need to move back.
Speaker 0: - Off of me.
Speaker 0: - You all get all around here.
Speaker 0: - You need to move back, please.
Speaker 0: - Get this girl out here.
Speaker 0: I have a right to be here.
Speaker 0: What, you gonna beat me with that?
Speaker 0: You gonna beat me with that?
Speaker 0: What?
Speaker 0: You're trying to outsmart me.
Speaker 0: - You heard me, well, no listen.
Speaker 0: - You gotta surrender.
Speaker 0: Is that your new whip?
Speaker 0: You want to whoop me with that?
Speaker 0: That's what I do with that.
Speaker 0: I got the right to be here just like you.
Speaker 0: You understand where we're coming from?
Speaker 0: You should be on this side.
Speaker 0: We just want to know if you know where we're coming from.
Speaker 0: You get the message of the protest?
Speaker 0: So why do we got to move?
Speaker 0: We got people coming from behind us too now.
Speaker 0: Like black people get attacked in the street and get killed.
Speaker 0: But why do we got to move?
Speaker 0: We have the right to be here.
Speaker 0: Because we have the currency back there.
Speaker 0: We got to move.
Speaker 0: We don't want to die in the streets.
Speaker 0: That's all we just said.
Speaker 0: I don't understand why you here.
Speaker 0: We can't get in.
Speaker 0: We got to get in.
Speaker 0: Is it hot for you to see shit?
Speaker 0: Like why do they got to do this shit?
Speaker 0: You guys stole it.
Speaker 0: What are you talking about you guys?
Speaker 0: You guys.
Speaker 0: I mean this is fucking useless.
Speaker 0: We got all these people coming behind us now.
Speaker 0: I mean what the fuck?
Speaker 0: You guys.
Speaker 0: You suckers.
Speaker 0: Look at all these fucking people coming out from behind us.
Speaker 0: This is fucking useless.
Speaker 0: We're just trying to keep up with them.
Speaker 0: But they're going to keep coming this way until we get the pop up there.
Speaker 0: I'm just going to walk kind of watch.
Speaker 0: All the way.
Speaker 0: Watch your back.
Speaker 0: We'll come behind you.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: We got to watch our back a little bit here.
Speaker 0: Go to Temple Street.
Speaker 0: It's good.
Speaker 0: Huh?
Speaker 0: Hey guys, let's get over here.
Speaker 0: There's a bunch of people coming in from behind us.
Speaker 0: Crap.
Speaker 0: Where's the other guys?
Speaker 0: Dudley, Kato and James huh?
Speaker 0: They might still be back on Winter Street.
Speaker 0: Where's James?
Speaker 0: All right.
Speaker 0: We're sitting ducks out in the middle of the fucking street like this.
Speaker 0: You know what?
Speaker 0: Go back that way.
Speaker 0: I got to get this car out of here.
Speaker 0: He's got a baby in the car.
Speaker 0: I want him out of here.
Speaker 0: Come on.
Speaker 0: Let this guy out of here.
Speaker 0: He's got a baby in the car.
Speaker 0: I want to get him out of here.
Speaker 0: Deputy.
Speaker 0: He's got a baby in the car.
Speaker 0: We got to get him out.
Speaker 0: He's coughing.
Speaker 0: He's fucking idiot.
Speaker 0: Go ahead.
Speaker 0: Just keep going nice and slow.
Speaker 0: All right.
Speaker 0: I got hit by a rock.
Speaker 0: Get him out of here.
Speaker 0: He's got a baby in the car.
Speaker 0: Put your lights on.
Speaker 0: Try to get him out of here.
Speaker 0: He's got a kid in the car.
Speaker 0: I'm trying to fuck him.
Speaker 0: Listen.
Speaker 0: You stay right behind her.
Speaker 0: She's going to try to get you out of here.
Speaker 0: All right?
Speaker 0: You stay right behind her.
Speaker 0: Where the fuck she went?
Speaker 0: They stayed back.
Speaker 0: Tell them to fucking stay behind her.
Speaker 0: Do what you can, Annie.
Speaker 0: Fuck it.
Speaker 0: What's up?
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 0: You should watch yourself.
Speaker 0: You shoot me in the face.
Speaker 0: You can't go one on one.
Speaker 0: Aaron, get out of here.
Speaker 0: You're going to fucking scare me.
Speaker 0: There you go.
Speaker 0: One on one.
Speaker 0: Fuck.
Speaker 0: Let's go.
Speaker 0: Oh, he's hit by a bottle.
Speaker 0: He's hit.
Speaker 0: You're fucking scared.
Speaker 0: No shit.
Speaker 0: We're just here.
Speaker 0: They're coming from behind us, too, now.
Speaker 0: We're sitting ducks over here like this.
Speaker 0: This is fucking nuts.
Speaker 0: We're sitting ducks like this in the fucking middle.
Speaker 0: We need to get the fuck out of here.
Speaker 0: What are we doing, Matt?
Speaker 0: We're fucking sitting ducks like this.
Speaker 0: Behind us.
Speaker 0: In front of us.
Speaker 0: Be advised.
Speaker 0: If you do not disperse... More fucking objects.
Speaker 0: You are hereby ordered by the state police to disperse.
Speaker 0: We will deploy the gas.
Speaker 0: Alright, yep.
Speaker 0: What's that?
Speaker 0: We're going to deploy your team.
Speaker 0: We're going to move forward.
Speaker 0: We're going to disperse.
Speaker 0: Alright?
Speaker 0: Stay tight.
Speaker 0: Why are you causing a traffic jam?
Speaker 0: You're in the middle of an intersection.
Speaker 0: What are you doing?
Speaker 0: Hold the line.
Speaker 0: Go.
Speaker 0: Get off.
Speaker 0: Get off and go.
Speaker 0: Go.
Speaker 0: They were leaving.
Speaker 0: That's why they're out of the park.
Speaker 0: Now you're moving them back to the park?
Speaker 0: They're fucking kids.
Speaker 0: The neighborhoods gave them love all day long.
Speaker 0: You know who didn't?
Speaker 0: These are fucking kids, man.
Speaker 0: Look at them.
Speaker 0: Show them where you are.
Speaker 0: They were leaving.
Speaker 0: That's why they're out of the park.
Speaker 0: Pause that.
Speaker 0: Be advised.
Speaker 0: We're standing here.
Speaker 0: I can't breathe.
Speaker 0: Idiots.
Speaker 0: Take some of these.
Speaker 0: Let me go home.
Speaker 0: Take a knee.
Speaker 0: Any of you guys.
Speaker 0: One.
Speaker 0: Take a knee.
Speaker 0: Just one.
Speaker 0: I'm not scared of you at all.
Speaker 0: Who do you serve?
Speaker 0: Hey, where's the sergeant?
Speaker 0: Move up.
Speaker 0: Move up the street.
Speaker 0: I just got to go.
Speaker 0: get my friend right here.
Speaker 0: Huh?
Speaker 0: Up the street.
Speaker 0: I just got to go.
Speaker 0: get my friend right here.
Speaker 0: Do you have kids?
Speaker 0: Up the street, please.
Speaker 0: Please move up the street, please.
Speaker 0: Just a simple question.
Speaker 0: Do you have kids?
Speaker 0: Please move up the street.
Speaker 0: Take a knee.
Speaker 0: Take a fucking knee right now.
Speaker 0: One of you take a fucking knee.
Speaker 0: Which one of you has a fucking heart?
Speaker 0: Which one of you has an actual?
Speaker 0: I'll bring it in.
Speaker 0: That's supposed to protect us, not kill us.
Speaker 0: For justice.
Speaker 0: We are here for you.
Speaker 0: We are here.
Speaker 0: I know I'm here for you.
Speaker 0: This is hard.
Speaker 0: Is the drain open?
Speaker 0: It didn't fucking work.
Speaker 0: We can blend the system.
Speaker 0: I'm not like any other man.
Speaker 0: You can still blame him.
Speaker 0: Let us celebrate!
Speaker 0: Yeah!
Speaker 0: Everybody on Tremont.
Speaker 0: Don and Gas Mask.
Speaker 0: I'm gonna shoot someone.
Speaker 0: What are they saying?
Speaker 0: Everyone on Tremont.
Speaker 0: Don and Gas Mask.
Speaker 0: That's fucking hard.
Speaker 0: I don't even have one.
Speaker 0: Shut up, Swindy.
Speaker 0: Get off the bus.
Speaker 0: Don't hit me.
Speaker 0: Gas Mask!
Speaker 0: Easy.
Speaker 0: [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO].
Speaker 0: [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO] [BLANK_AUDIO].