Speaker 0: [BEEPING] Cameras.
Speaker 0: All right, we've got my squad over here.
Speaker 0: We're just going to parachute them down the street.
Speaker 0: So kind of form up in a line.
Speaker 0: Jay, I'm on the other side.
Speaker 0: Tech man.
Speaker 0: [INTERPOSING VOICES].
Speaker 0: I'm attacked.
Speaker 0: You've got to put your job, man.
Speaker 0: It's not you.
Speaker 0: [INTERPOSING VOICES].
Speaker 0: Squadron, exit area.
Speaker 0: What do you got?
Speaker 0: [INTERPOSING VOICES].
Speaker 0: [INTERPOSING VOICES] [BEEPING] [BEEPING].
Speaker 0: Hey, guys, keep it tight.
Speaker 0: Keep it tight.
Speaker 0: [INTERPOSING VOICES].
Speaker 0: How many more people?
Speaker 0: [BEEPING] [INTERPOSING VOICES] [INTERPOSING VOICES] [BEEPING].
Speaker 0: Guys, turn and face that way.
Speaker 0: [INTERPOSING VOICES].
Speaker 0: [INTERPOSING VOICES] >> [INAUDIBLE].
Speaker 0: >> Where's McGrail?
Speaker 0: >> I think he's down on his head.
Speaker 0: >> Are you in his squad?
Speaker 0: >> Huh?
Speaker 0: >> I'm in Hogan's squad.
Speaker 0: >> Line together, put the line together.
Speaker 0: >> Where's McGrail?
Speaker 0: >> [INAUDIBLE].
Speaker 0: >> All right, what's that Brian?
Speaker 0: >> There we go, there we go.
Speaker 0: Nobody through.
Speaker 0: >> [INAUDIBLE].
Speaker 0: >> I'm working on a cap, and I'll advise the LECC.
Speaker 0: we need help down there.
Speaker 0: They're throwing bricks now at the opposite.
Speaker 0: >> [INAUDIBLE].
Speaker 0: >> I'll check on it.
Speaker 0: >> Several vehicles damaged there.
Speaker 0: >> [INAUDIBLE].
Speaker 0: >> Shit, Tom, you find another way.
Speaker 0: >> What group do you have up there now, cap?
Speaker 0: >> [INAUDIBLE].
Speaker 0: >> About 80, okay.
Speaker 0: >> LECC to Operation.
Speaker 0: >> Entering the LECC.
Speaker 0: >> Sir, you got the state police on the way for you now, Dr.
Speaker 0: Newberry.
Speaker 0: >> State police coming to New Brea and Exeter, thank you.
Speaker 0: >> Charlie four.
Speaker 0: >> Okay, sir, we got your one up to stage on Huntington Ave, is that correct?
Speaker 0: >> The Exeter people are now loading the store now.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, we don't have anybody down there.
Speaker 0: We're up at Exeter.
Speaker 0: >> They have it.
Speaker 0: >> What's that?
Speaker 0: >> Strap me up.
Speaker 0: >> It came out.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> You can just set up other black people.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, good.
Speaker 0: Hold it up right here.
Speaker 0: Don't get further.
Speaker 0: >> Any injuries or anything like that?
Speaker 0: >> [INAUDIBLE].
Speaker 0: >> People are happy to do what the fuck they're doing right now.
Speaker 0: [BUZZER].
Speaker 0: >> Sir, that stranger is being killed.
Speaker 0: And y'all don't do nothing about it.
Speaker 0: >> [INAUDIBLE].
Speaker 0: >> Fuck your fraternity.
Speaker 0: Fuck your fraternity, bro.
Speaker 0: The real fraternity is fucking human rights.
Speaker 0: I ain't doing shit to change it.
Speaker 0: I ain't doing nothing.
Speaker 0: Besides, how many--.
Speaker 0: >> Look, this plot thing came out of the buckle.
Speaker 0: You'd have to take it off to fix it.
Speaker 0: >> All right.
Speaker 0: >> Delta
Speaker 0: 903. >>
Speaker 0: Newberry and Clarence are trying to make an arrest.
Speaker 0: Do you need a car?
Speaker 0: >> Delta 908.
Speaker 0: [INAUDIBLE].
Speaker 0: >> Delta 903.
Speaker 0: This is Zara stores.
Speaker 0: Z-A-R-A.
Speaker 0: I'll be there in one second.
Speaker 0: >> 212 Newberry.
Speaker 0: >> Z-A-R-A stores.
Speaker 0: >> Store.
Speaker 0: >> Is McGregor around there?
Speaker 0: >> McVernon.
Speaker 0: >> Are we able to get fire in there at all with the crowd?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, Steve, get over there.
Speaker 0: >> They're on their way.
Speaker 0: 212 Newberry is there.
Speaker 0: >> Delta 902.
Speaker 0: I'll be told if somebody put the fire out with a fire extinguisher.
Speaker 0: Some guys are going to go in there and take a look at it now.
Speaker 0: But still haven't come in here.
Speaker 0: >> They're fucking cowards.
Speaker 0: >> Working on it right now.
Speaker 0: >> It's a fucking little dress.
Speaker 0: >> You want it for a second?
Speaker 0: >> No need to go in there.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, don't breathe this shit in.
Speaker 0: >> I do not suck.
Speaker 0: I'm up on channel 1.
Speaker 0: [INTERPOSING VOICES].
Speaker 0: >> That was a black body hanging.
Speaker 0: We're doing shit right now.
Speaker 0: [INAUDIBLE].
Speaker 0: >> So you can.
Speaker 0: >> Show us that you can.
Speaker 0: >> They need a car to clear up a 780 Boylston.
Speaker 0: Attacking the workers.
Speaker 0: We're trying to put the door up.
Speaker 0: >> I know you've seen the video.
Speaker 0: >> We got the blinker.
Speaker 0: >> As a black man.
Speaker 0: Not even as a police officer.
Speaker 0: As a black man.
Speaker 0: >> Rail is elusive.
Speaker 0: I don't know where he fucking went.
Speaker 0: >> Rich Hardy's is being looted now.
Speaker 0: >> That's behind us.
Speaker 0: >> Whiskey Mike 1 on Delta.
Speaker 0: >> Whiskey Mike
Speaker 0: 1. >>
Speaker 0: Sir, could you advise if you got a fire, a call for a fire on Boylston 212 Eastbury?
Speaker 0: >> I do, sir.
Speaker 0: Fire's on the way.
Speaker 0: >> But you said you're not doing shit.
Speaker 0: >> That's Steve.
Speaker 0: They're still in Huntington.
Speaker 0: They're like Berkeley and Newbury.
Speaker 0: >> Berkeley and Newbury.
Speaker 0: I'll get them.
Speaker 0: >> And that is not this.
Speaker 0: >> All right, fire's got the call for 212 Newbury, but they want a crew to escort them out of the firehouse there at Boylston and Hereford.
Speaker 0: >> Are you kidding me?
Speaker 0: >> We need an ambulance to Tremont and Temple Place.
Speaker 0: >> Keep your eyes open.
Speaker 0: >> Tremont and Temple Place.
Speaker 0: You need an ambulance.
Speaker 0: Come up on Channel
Speaker 0: 1. >>
Speaker 0: We got an officer down on a fire rescue, but he won't arrive that soon.
Speaker 0: >> An officer down at Tremont and Temple Place.
Speaker 0: >> Huh?
Speaker 0: >> McGrail?
Speaker 0: >> No.
Speaker 0: >> He's probably back there.
Speaker 0: I thought he'd come over here, so why can't he?
Speaker 0: >> Right there.
Speaker 0: >> Right?
Speaker 0: >> No, that's Aziz.
Speaker 0: >> No, I don't know who that is.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, it's a six-digit number.
Speaker 0: I don't think that's Hogarth.
Speaker 0: >> McGrail doesn't have a vest on.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, it's quite about 2-3.
Speaker 0: >> Everything's out of this burden?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> Where's the fire?
Speaker 0: >> Let's wait till they leave.
Speaker 0: >> So you just seen that, right?
Speaker 0: Don't act like you ain't just seen that.
Speaker 0: You didn't just see that shit?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> So you just seen the waters end up on the wall like, "Huh?
Speaker 0: Huh?".
Speaker 0: >> What's up, guys?
Speaker 0: >> I wouldn't have to do a forced entry on this, right?
Speaker 0: Because the window was already broken.
Speaker 0: >> Right.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, no, you know what?
Speaker 0: You know what?
Speaker 0: >> No.
Speaker 0: >> Can I just leave you?
Speaker 0: >> You've got to go 30 o'clock ahead.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> See?
Speaker 0: >> Thank you, Elvin.
Speaker 0: >> That was the same person.
Speaker 0: >> But then the captain told me after that.
Speaker 0: >> The only one.
Speaker 0: >> He's like, "I'm trying to
Speaker 0: drill.".
Speaker 0: >> That was the last captain, yeah.
Speaker 0: >> Staff units in the oil center.
Speaker 0: I'll correct that.
Speaker 0: Newberry and Exeter, Captain.
Speaker 0: >> Last staff units to come in now.
Speaker 0: >> Where are we at?
Speaker 0: >> Huh?
Speaker 0: >> You're so elusive.
Speaker 0: I've lost you like nine times.
Speaker 0: >> I meant to move my cruiser.
Speaker 0: >> Where are we?
Speaker 0: >> I locked it, too, even though all the windows are broken out.
Speaker 0: >> Was yours the one on Newberry?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> That was the spare cruiser, though.
Speaker 0: I took it because it didn't have the shotgun.
Speaker 0: >> Did you grab anything in there?
Speaker 0: >> Huh?
Speaker 0: >> No.
Speaker 0: >> Somebody's about to give me $1.89 because he wanted to push me.
Speaker 0: >> You got it on the board as well?
Speaker 0: >> No.
Speaker 0: >> We need a squad down at the oil center on Ring Road.
Speaker 0: We have a crew trying to break in the store.
Speaker 0: They're also attacking the people that are putting up the boarding.
Speaker 0: >> Is your mouth shut?
Speaker 0: >> It's my mouth shut as well.
Speaker 0: >> Delta 9-0-2, fire's clearing off at 2-12 Newberry.
Speaker 0: >> It's clearing out at 2-12 Newberry.
Speaker 0: >> You got a
Speaker 0: $1.89? >>
Speaker 0: You want a new gun?
Speaker 0: >> When he comes out, y'all don't run up on me with a baton.
Speaker 0: >> Put a gun in the hand of the guy.
Speaker 0: >> I'm always sober.
Speaker 0: I've been again for a while.
Speaker 0: >> Alright, 5-0-1 Boylston coming in now.
Speaker 0: They're trying to break in the glass doors there.
Speaker 0: >> Hey, I'm stealing some of you guys to go with the captain.
Speaker 0: I'm stealing some of you guys to go with the captain for the super.
Speaker 0: >> Hey, guys.
Speaker 0: >> Obviously, everybody's got to stay together.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, they should hire more cops.
Speaker 0: >> What is that for?
Speaker 0: >> I don't know.
Speaker 0: >> Hey, I caught the large group in the sun market.
Speaker 0: Now, is that correct?
Speaker 0: >> Delta Base, can you give me UPD?
Speaker 0: Two hard toes over the massive Harrison in the NBA.
Speaker 0: >> You leave it on the whole fucking time.
Speaker 0: You leave it on the whole time.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, no, no.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, yeah.
Speaker 0: >> Negative.
Speaker 0: >> Alpha
Speaker 0: 3. >>
Speaker 0: We have that.
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 0: >> Kilo 102 up to ring road.
Speaker 0: >> Ring road at 6.
Speaker 0: One coming out the door now.
Speaker 0: >> 240 Newbury is a CVS.
Speaker 0: They're trying to smash the doors now with a baseball bat.
Speaker 0: >> Five, nine, nine.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, I got it.
Speaker 0: >> I'm on the lead activity.
Speaker 0: >> Radio 95-18.
Speaker 0: Four officers injured.
Speaker 0: >> What do you got going there?
Speaker 0: >> They're still looted in the building.
Speaker 0: >> Okay.
Speaker 0: >> Are you in the building?
Speaker 0: >> Yes, sir.
Speaker 0: Me and five other officers.
Speaker 0: >> How many people in there?
Speaker 0: >> That's unknown right now, sir.
Speaker 0: >> 760 Boylston, Lord and Taylor being looted at this time.
Speaker 0: I got a group of 50 in there.
Speaker 0: >> Benny, is that you and Sacks?
Speaker 0: >> Yes, sir.
Speaker 0: >> Okay, I don't want you guys to get caught up in this.
Speaker 0: Let's make your way out to ring road and just have a line right there outside the door.
Speaker 0: >> I have it.
Speaker 0: >> Is anyone still at SOM office?
Speaker 0: >> Documenting.
Speaker 0: >> Peaceful protest.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> Benny, there's a group coming up towards you, towards Star Market.
Speaker 0: Keep you updated.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> There's new.
Speaker 0: >> Did you hear some lady like driving by when we were walking away?
Speaker 0: She like rolled her window down.
Speaker 0: She's like... >> They're looting whatever address.
Speaker 0: >> You don't say.
Speaker 0: >> I go, yeah, maybe they should have hired more cops.
Speaker 0: >> What do you want?
Speaker 0: >> These guys?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> We're all working at this time, but I can certainly make some phone calls.
Speaker 0: >> That's
Speaker 0: 12. >>
Speaker 0: You got any glue?
Speaker 0: >> Why do they break into some places and not others, like that Zara?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> I don't think anybody even shops there.
Speaker 0: It's like European people.
Speaker 0: >> Which store, sir?
Speaker 0: >> Oh, I thought he was chasing that car.
Speaker 0: >> Matt, take a squad down there.
Speaker 0: Just look out for the Leonard.
Speaker 0: >> Got it.
Speaker 0: >> And have the D14 cop hang around.
Speaker 0: We can put it in the lot right here.
Speaker 0: >> I didn't even notice.
Speaker 0: >> Delta 908, I'm taking a squad to Boyle Center and Exeter.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, yeah.
Speaker 0: >> He's like, "Leave me
Speaker 0: alone.".
Speaker 0: >> Did Z4 survive?
Speaker 0: >> What?
Speaker 0: >> Did the district survive?
Speaker 0: >> Do we have anybody left on Newbury?
Speaker 0: It's on the lower end at this time.
Speaker 0: >> Steve, no one from us.
Speaker 0: What do you got?
Speaker 0: >> 115 Newbury at the Rag and Bone.
Speaker 0: They're breaking in now.
Speaker 0: They've smashed the windows and they're losing the place.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, man.
Speaker 0: >> Fighters.
Speaker 0: >> Okay.
Speaker 0: >> Did you see Z4?
Speaker 0: >> No.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, did the state get on that?
Speaker 0: >> First and... >> Jack, I have three with me here on Ring Road.
Speaker 0: >> Z4?
Speaker 0: >> I'm off the next few days.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, me too.
Speaker 0: >> Unless they order me tonight.
Speaker 0: >> Adam, we've been over to Ring Road.
Speaker 0: >> All right.
Speaker 0: >> I've got five officers.
Speaker 0: I'm going to walk down that way from Exeter Street.
Speaker 0: >> Okay, coming in from Exeter Street.
Speaker 0: >> Victor Alpha Nine, operating.
Speaker 0: >> Victor Alpha Nine.
Speaker 0: >> If you want me on on A or E and D, you can leave the P.S.
Speaker 0: on either side if you need me.
Speaker 0: >> Thank you.
Speaker 0: Well, take it easy.
Speaker 0: >> Alpha Nine, I don't want to start.
Speaker 0: >> Nine Oh One, good evening.
Speaker 0: >> We could see a lot of smoke as we're approaching it.
Speaker 0: >> Give me a fix on a good address, Super.
Speaker 0: I'll get fired down there.
Speaker 0: I've got numerous shops down there that are being looted.
Speaker 0: >> Permits is looking good now.
Speaker 0: >> We're getting activity down the lower end there.
Speaker 0: 116 Newbury, 75 Newbury, 2 Newbury, 79 Newbury.
Speaker 0: >> I'm sorry.
Speaker 0: >> Delta Charlie One, can you loosen up those troopers?
Speaker 0: Have them move over to Newbury Street or are you using them now?
Speaker 0: >> I'm coming in for the last to settle down there with Sergeant McManus.
Speaker 0: >> Okay, very good.
Speaker 0: >> I'd advise they're going to be on foot coming down here.
Speaker 0: >> Three troopers coming on foot.
Speaker 0: >> Call now for shots fired at Dartmouth and Newbury with subjects looting the store there on Longwich Store.
Speaker 0: >> And I need one other person.
Speaker 0: >> Delta Charlie One, the Captain Tweedy's coming over.
Speaker 0: He's going to be in charge of you guys, okay?
Speaker 0: >> Oh, you know what?
Speaker 0: Hey, he's right over here.
Speaker 0: Just meet up with him.
Speaker 0: >> Great large group starting to disperse.
Speaker 0: You may eye contact with you.
Speaker 0: You're approaching Clarendon Street.
Speaker 0: >> Tweedy, how many total do you have on both sides?
Speaker 0: >> We only have five officers on Ring Road, Star Market side.
Speaker 0: >> I'm sorry, come again?
Speaker 0: How many officers is there?
Speaker 0: >> Five officers.
Speaker 0: >> Keep back, select Clarendon Street.
Speaker 0: We're going to need more help.
Speaker 0: Push them out of here.
Speaker 0: >> Okay, Super, they're retreating slowly back to Clarendon.
Speaker 0: >> I've got troopers coming in on foot and I've got other officers coming in from the four, District Four.
Speaker 0: >> 903. >>
Speaker 0: Okay, I've got myself, Tweedy, officers in my state here at Newbury.
Speaker 0: >> If you've got enough on there, they can use your Yankee C4, pushing the group back up to Clarendon Street.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> Guys, you want to come this way with us?
Speaker 0: >> Fuck 'em.
Speaker 0: >> Rental.
Speaker 0: For rental.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> You guys see that fucking Yankee C3 anywhere?
Speaker 0: >> What are they, yellow vests, right?
Speaker 0: >> Yankee C4.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> So ridiculous.
Speaker 0: >> This is when you know you don't have a successful business.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> They're pushing water up off the hill.
Speaker 0: >> It's like bailing out a boat with a hole still in it.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> We got the four.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> Large group moving back towards Lloyd and Taylor.
Speaker 0: >> I can't wait to go to 911 calls after this and be like, "I don't give a fuck about
Speaker 0: you.".
Speaker 0: >> Huh?
Speaker 0: >> Like, go into a call after this.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> Be like, "Fuck off.
Speaker 0: You got
Speaker 0: nothing.".
Speaker 0: >> It isn't you, sir.
Speaker 0: 5465.
Speaker 0: We got very heavy traffic up here.
Speaker 0: Stand by.
Speaker 0: >> What's that?
Speaker 0: >> Delta
Speaker 0: 901. >>
Speaker 0: Stand by.
Speaker 0: AKC 4, what's your situation?
Speaker 0: [horn honks].
Speaker 0: >> Uh, it's clear.
Speaker 0: >> All right, Delta 908, how are you making out, sir?
Speaker 0: [horn honks].
Speaker 0: >> Delta Charlie 1, how are you doing?
Speaker 0: [horn honks] [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> It's like a bird.
Speaker 0: >> What is that?
Speaker 0: What just happened?
Speaker 0: >> He's got a bunch of stuff in the back.
Speaker 0: >> Trooper!
Speaker 0: [horn honks] [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> What's that?
Speaker 0: >> He needs to take a break.
Speaker 0: Exhausted.
Speaker 0: >> Maybe they'll break into a CVS and we can go in and get some water.
Speaker 0: >> I know.
Speaker 0: >> I'm sure they have already.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: [horn honks].
Speaker 0: >> It's sealed.
Speaker 0: >> Delta Charlie 1, where are you now, Captain?
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> You guys good?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, thank you, thank you.
Speaker 0: >> Where's your brother?
Speaker 0: >> It's crazy.
Speaker 0: He's in the other side.
Speaker 0: We're protecting our stores, man.
Speaker 0: This thing is crazy.
Speaker 0: It's like, we were in downtown.
Speaker 0: It started in downtown, right?
Speaker 0: Thank God I boarded this fucking store.
Speaker 0: >> I know.
Speaker 0: >> Then we came here.
Speaker 0: We're like, all right, everyone's coming here.
Speaker 0: Now we're protecting our stores here.
Speaker 0: >> All right, stay safe, all right?
Speaker 0: >> Thank you, brother.
Speaker 0: >> See you.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> I'm just thinking.
Speaker 0: That's why I was going back, but then... >> Oh, sorry.
Speaker 0: >> Do you have to tie your shoe?
Speaker 0: >> No, I know that guy.
Speaker 0: >> Oh.
Speaker 0: >> He owns the smoke shop.
Speaker 0: >> Was it water, at least?
Speaker 0: >> No, it wasn't that.
Speaker 0: >> It was water.
Speaker 0: >> It's sealed, so... >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter] [horn honks].
Speaker 0: >> I said the captain's that boss on that trip.
Speaker 0: [horn honks].
Speaker 0: >> They even took the license plate off the van.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> Captain, we're at Berkeley right now.
Speaker 0: Between Berkeley and Arlington.
Speaker 0: >> I have it.
Speaker 0: >> Brian McGrail, your location?
Speaker 0: >> 211 Newberry, Delta
Speaker 0: 903. >>
Speaker 0: It came over?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> Delta 903, 211 Newberry.
Speaker 0: >> Guys, one sec.
Speaker 0: >> You got anything going on there right now?
Speaker 0: >> It's just like, uh... >> Yeah, Berlin people along.
Speaker 0: As we walk, they come out of this door to move.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, we can do that.
Speaker 0: >> Brian, do that for me.
Speaker 0: See what you got.
Speaker 0: >> Captain, he's like... Uh, do you want to head over to the Copley Square Mall?
Speaker 0: >> Absolutely.
Speaker 0: >> All right.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter] [laughter].
Speaker 0: >> It's a new CSO van, too, huh?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, of course.
Speaker 0: 2200 miles.
Speaker 0: >> Probably get a new one in four years.
Speaker 0: >> What's up?
Speaker 0: Hold on.
Speaker 0: What's that?
Speaker 0: Cull?
Speaker 0: >> Okay.
Speaker 0: >> Oh.
Speaker 0: No, one of the B2B guys is standing in front of us.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> Oh, you're the fucking boss.
Speaker 0: Is that somebody's duty bag?
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> I can take that out of the back of the van?
Speaker 0: Hope we didn't have anything crazy in there.
Speaker 0: >> Where's the van now?
Speaker 0: >> Right back here.
Speaker 0: No, I'll take it back over, I guess.
Speaker 0: >> This one?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: Hey, you said to the Copley Square Park?
Speaker 0: >> Guys, watch these vehicles.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> What's the location for the RITO again?
Speaker 0: >> Berkeley and Newberry.
Speaker 0: Berkeley and Newberry.
Speaker 0: >> Okay, I have that.
Speaker 0: >> Mansion, Newberry.
Speaker 0: >> Deploy back down.
Speaker 0: >> Just have presence up there.
Speaker 0: Should keep them out of there, yeah?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, I got a group coming in from Brookline as well.
Speaker 0: They're staging Mansion, Newberry.
Speaker 0: >> All right, link on here first.
Speaker 0: So I sent them up there.
Speaker 0: >> Okay, do you need help down where you are?
Speaker 0: >> Get him, get him, get him!
Speaker 0: >> Send Brookline down, I like... Send them to the captain off Boylston Street.
Speaker 0: Boylston and Ring Road then.
Speaker 0: >> Okay, will do.
Speaker 0: >> Delta Base, Delta 910.
Speaker 0: D and G, tone on the way.
Speaker 0: Okay, there's two officers standing by there now.
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 0: >> I'm just going to head up to the stacks.
Speaker 0: >> Not sure if it's already on the board, but we just got a call about North Face on Newberry Street being loaded.
Speaker 0: >> Multiple alarm calls on loading up and down Newberry.
Speaker 0: >> Vehicles here.
Speaker 0: We won't let any traffic say Berkeley and Newberry.
Speaker 0: We'll shut it down there.
Speaker 0: We won't let anybody up.
Speaker 0: >> We're going to close off Newberry altogether at Berkeley Street.
Speaker 0: >> Desi, wait up.
Speaker 0: >> Hey, this is the whole mall, right?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, where you guys trying to go?
Speaker 0: >> Anywhere.
Speaker 0: >> Boylston Street?
Speaker 0: >> We just want to walk through and see if we can find anybody.
Speaker 0: >> We got it pretty tight in here.
Speaker 0: Nobody's coming in here.
Speaker 0: >> This one particular spot, though, right?
Speaker 0: >> This whole mall.
Speaker 0: We got about 15 guys inside here.
Speaker 0: >> Okay.
Speaker 0: >> They did hit Lord and Taylor's and Shaw's.
Speaker 0: They've been hitting Starr.
Speaker 0: They've been going in and out.
Speaker 0: >> All right, so otherwise you guys are secure.
Speaker 0: >> This is tight.
Speaker 0: We got a lot of people in here.
Speaker 0: >> All right.
Speaker 0: >> They've been staying out.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, it's the whole fucking street, Steve.
Speaker 0: [wind blowing].
Speaker 0: >> Hands behind your back.
Speaker 0: Hands behind your back.
Speaker 0: >> No.
Speaker 0: >> Just sit down.
Speaker 0: >> Can I turn around a little bit, please?
Speaker 0: [beeping] >> Let's get you set up, all right?
Speaker 0: >> Good job.
Speaker 0: All right, I'm going to head down to the fourth side.
Speaker 0: >> Okay.
Speaker 0: >> What do you guys want to do with this guy?
Speaker 0: >> What are we doing with this guy?
Speaker 0: >> You can't say what we're doing.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> Tell me what you want.
Speaker 0: >> What's your record looking like?
Speaker 0: >> All right.
Speaker 0: >> This is not bad.
Speaker 0: How many guns?
Speaker 0: >> I just caught one last few months ago, but I can do this.
Speaker 0: >> What do you think this is?
Speaker 0: I'll take it, Brian.
Speaker 0: >> All right.
Speaker 0: >> I'll charge him with domestic terrorism.
Speaker 0: >> Who is this?
Speaker 0: >> Huh?
Speaker 0: >> Who's Elmita?
Speaker 0: >> He walked out.
Speaker 0: [beeping].
Speaker 0: >> All right, so we can shut it down at Diamond and St.
Speaker 0: James and keep it from coming up to Boyle to Donover?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, yeah.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, we want to form a perimeter around this entire area for vehicle traffic.
Speaker 0: >> A perimeter to exclude vehicle traffic.
Speaker 0: >> Okay.
Speaker 0: What's up?
Speaker 0: Looting, trespassing, breaking and entering at night, domestic terrorism, inciting a riot.
Speaker 0: >> What he's doing is being charged with.
Speaker 0: >> All right, calm down.
Speaker 0: >> What's he doing?
Speaker 0: >> District 4.
Speaker 0: Unless they're taking him, Brian.
Speaker 0: >> Do you want this or no?
Speaker 0: Because we can just cut him in half.
Speaker 0: >> I mean, it's the fucking city's on fire, so.
Speaker 0: >> I'll summon someone.
Speaker 0: >> Okay.
Speaker 0: >> Listen.
Speaker 0: >> Who's your brother?
Speaker 0: >> Oh, no.
Speaker 0: >> Okay, you got a phone on you?
Speaker 0: >> No, I don't know.
Speaker 0: >> This is it.
Speaker 0: >> We're going to take him in.
Speaker 0: >> We're going to release you.
Speaker 0: >> You're going to be summoned?
Speaker 0: >> You're going to be summoned.
Speaker 0: [beeping].
Speaker 0: >> You say you're out because of Rollins?
Speaker 0: >> Huh?
Speaker 0: >> What did you just say?
Speaker 0: >> No, I said.
Speaker 0: If you guys want to see me at some point, you can take me to jail.
Speaker 0: I got a gun charger.
Speaker 0: >> What's your first name?
Speaker 0: >> Jakari.
Speaker 0: T-A-K-A-R-I.
Speaker 0: >> Last name?
Speaker 0: >> H-O-K-E-T-T.
Speaker 0: >> Birthday?
Speaker 0: >> 7-22-02.
Speaker 0: You hear me?
Speaker 0: 7-22-02.
Speaker 0: >> I got you.
Speaker 0: You got a phone?
Speaker 0: >> Um, 8-5-7.
Speaker 0: 3-0-9.
Speaker 0: 0-5-0-5.
Speaker 0: >> Where do you live at?
Speaker 0: >> 51 Regent Street.
Speaker 0: Is there someplace we can fucking throw all this shit?
Speaker 0: >> Bring it back.
Speaker 0: The lady from the store is right there.
Speaker 0: >> Put it in this box?
Speaker 0: >> They won't move it.
Speaker 0: They'll walk you back over to the store.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, there we go.
Speaker 0: First.
Speaker 0: >> You mean AA and Avalon over here?
Speaker 0: I saw the whole thing from the beginning.
Speaker 0: From when they broke the glass in and they ran in there.
Speaker 0: I saw the whole thing.
Speaker 0: I was out on my deck.
Speaker 0: If I had one of your sticks, I'd love one of your sticks.
Speaker 0: >> You can have it and do this job.
Speaker 0: >> Do you have an extra stick?
Speaker 0: >> Uh, they stole them all out of our van.
Speaker 0: I'm sure you can find them on the street somewhere.
Speaker 0: >> I'm sorry.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, we're all set.
Speaker 0: We don't need any more.
Speaker 0: >> I used to have your Smith & Wesson 38 Special.
Speaker 0: >> Nice.
Speaker 0: >> I used to live in Miami.
Speaker 0: It's a long story, but my friend in Ohio said you'd better get one.
Speaker 0: One of my students came in and tried to rob me.
Speaker 0: I sat there with my gun and said, "You come in this
Speaker 0: apartment.".
Speaker 0: >> You got what you need from him?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> Somebody get the cuffs off him?
Speaker 0: >> I'm just going to bring it back in the slot.
Speaker 0: >> It's like 60 wretches in the apartment.
Speaker 0: >> I apologize.
Speaker 0: >> Why don't you go smash up some windows and loot around Roxbury?
Speaker 0: >> Hey, go home.
Speaker 0: >> Please.
Speaker 0: >> Thanks.
Speaker 0: >> Thank you.
Speaker 0: >> Brian, I'm going to bring this back into the slot.
Speaker 0: >> I'm not writing this.
Speaker 0: >> No, you're not writing it.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> Well, when he zigged, I was like, "I'm going to get this
Speaker 0: motherfucker.".
Speaker 0: >> Watch your feet, man.
Speaker 0: >> No.
Speaker 0: >> You don't want it?
Speaker 0: >> You can take it if you want.
Speaker 0: >> All right, no pedestrians, no cars on Newbury unless they live there.
Speaker 0: We also advise the alarm companies to not have their runners come in for their own safety.
Speaker 0: [phone ringing].
Speaker 0: >> Your deal is.
Speaker 0: none of this is without my hand.
Speaker 0: >> Right?
Speaker 0: This is all that's yours.
Speaker 0: >> I'm telling you.
Speaker 0: >> I get you, but just be careful, okay?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, can I have your stick?
Speaker 0: >> Take the hammer.
Speaker 0: >> There you go.
Speaker 0: >> Do more damage.
Speaker 0: >> No, this is the hammer that had the postman broke his.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, but the... >> It's a souvenir.
Speaker 0: >> There you go.
Speaker 0: [wind blowing].
Speaker 0: >> Dude, look at that.
Speaker 0: Like, all of his skin came off.
Speaker 0: He's down to the bone.
Speaker 0: [chatter].
Speaker 0: >> Hey, what's your name?
Speaker 0: >> Jason.
Speaker 0: [chatter].
Speaker 0: >> Where do you live?
Speaker 0: >> How do you spell Canabur?
Speaker 0: >> J-A-N-T-E-B-U-R.
Speaker 0: >> Hey, let him go.
Speaker 0: [horn honking].
Speaker 0: [chatter].
Speaker 0: >> I might go grab a water.
Speaker 0: >> Why not?
Speaker 0: >> Are you a representative, Sean?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, I work for the company.
Speaker 0: >> You think I can get a cup of band-aids?
Speaker 0: >> Let me go over to these guys.
Speaker 0: >> Okay, Joe.
Speaker 0: >> A girl slipped just now, almost cut her whole neck.
Speaker 0: >> Stand by, I'm working on one right now.
Speaker 0: >> This girl almost cut her whole neck.
Speaker 0: >> Did she break the window?
Speaker 0: >> When she was coming down, she slipped, and her neck went like this.
Speaker 0: >> Oh.
Speaker 0: >> She was very lucky.
Speaker 0: >> Jesus.
Speaker 0: >> Be careful.
Speaker 0: >> Is that necessary?
Speaker 0: [chatter].
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, yeah, yeah, exactly.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> Look, I usually go with band-aid brands.
Speaker 0: >> Tough strips.
Speaker 0: >> Tough strips, there you go.
Speaker 0: >> Those are the best ones.
Speaker 0: >> AKC4.
Speaker 0: >> AKC4, big ones.
Speaker 0: [chatter].
Speaker 0: >> I just need a couple out of them.
Speaker 0: >> No, we can't sell it.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, well, I'm not going to carry the whole thing around with me all night.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, Bobby.
Speaker 0: Put some in your pocket because you need to change.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, you know what?
Speaker 0: Thank you very much.
Speaker 0: >> That's a good idea.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, you need to change it.
Speaker 0: >> Is there a sink you can wash it?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: [chatter].
Speaker 0: >> Be careful.
Speaker 0: >> I think I can grab a water.
Speaker 0: [chatter].
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, go ahead, go ahead.
Speaker 0: [chatter] >> All right, I also need the side streets off of Karma.
Speaker 0: I've blocked off so they don't feed into Nubre.
Speaker 0: >> Is there somebody in here?
Speaker 0: [chatter].
Speaker 0: >> You know what, man?
Speaker 0: Fuck it, I'm fine.
Speaker 0: I'm just going to throw a Band-Aid on it.
Speaker 0: >> No, dude.
Speaker 0: You should have taken alcohol, too.
Speaker 0: >> You sure?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> All right.
Speaker 0: Alcohol is good.
Speaker 0: >> I hear that, but usually not the kind you put on your finger, right?
Speaker 0: >> I don't want to drink.
Speaker 0: >> You know what I'm talking about.
Speaker 0: You want to clean a... [chatter] >> Yeah, I just live in the area.
Speaker 0: I got some Band-Aid.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, thank you.
Speaker 0: >> So I live in the area.
Speaker 0: I know the area very well.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, no problem.
Speaker 0: [chatter].
Speaker 0: >> Thanks again.
Speaker 0: >> Okay.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> Is he in here?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, I think he went in already.
Speaker 0: [chatter].
Speaker 0: >> You're going to get some.
Speaker 0: >> I'm just going to sit down.
Speaker 0: I'm going to sit down.
Speaker 0: [chatter].
Speaker 0: >> I'm down.
Speaker 0: I'm trying to get my food.
Speaker 0: >> Stay down.
Speaker 0: >> I'm down.
Speaker 0: I'm down right now.
Speaker 0: >> Get on your stomach.
Speaker 0: Get your hands down.
Speaker 0: >> Okay, I'm down.
Speaker 0: >> Get your hands down.
Speaker 0: >> Get my hands down.
Speaker 0: You asked me to drop everything.
Speaker 0: I drop everything.
Speaker 0: You asked me to leave, and I'm leaving.
Speaker 0: >> And then you ranch in your pocket.
Speaker 0: >> Roll over.
Speaker 0: >> No, I ain't--.
Speaker 0: >> Are we copping him, or--?
Speaker 0: >> No, I ain't doing nothing.
Speaker 0: >> Roll over, sir.
Speaker 0: >> Get on your stomach.
Speaker 0: >> Roll over.
Speaker 0: >> Okay, I'm not rolling over.
Speaker 0: So how the fuck am I going to roll over?
Speaker 0: [chatter].
Speaker 0: >> There you go.
Speaker 0: This asshole is going.
Speaker 0: >> Move his shirt up.
Speaker 0: >> Guys.
Speaker 0: Hey, troopers on.
Speaker 0: Any keys to those dressing rooms?
Speaker 0: Or boots?
Speaker 0: In here, on the ground?
Speaker 0: >> Can I get on now?
Speaker 0: Can I get on now?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, yeah, I've got nothing except for my house keys and my phone.
Speaker 0: Somebody got my phone.
Speaker 0: >> Can I get my phone?
Speaker 0: Can I get my phone, sir?
Speaker 0: Can I get my passport?
Speaker 0: >> No, no.
Speaker 0: >> Why not?
Speaker 0: [phone ringing].
Speaker 0: >> That's what I was doing.
Speaker 0: That's what I was doing.
Speaker 0: >> He's already too tight.
Speaker 0: >> Whoa.
Speaker 0: >> I'm not moving around.
Speaker 0: >> Okay, I'm not moving around.
Speaker 0: >> He's already tight.
Speaker 0: >> May I have my phone back?
Speaker 0: >> No.
Speaker 0: >> That's my property.
Speaker 0: >> This is somebody else's property.
Speaker 0: This isn't your property.
Speaker 0: He respects people's property, right?
Speaker 0: Looting.
Speaker 0: He's a clown.
Speaker 0: Absolute clown.
Speaker 0: [knocking].
Speaker 0: >> They took the register over there.
Speaker 0: >> Why, is there somebody in there?
Speaker 0: >> Well, I couldn't get the doors open, so there could be.
Speaker 0: >> They're probably on somebody's key chain.
Speaker 0: [phone ringing].
Speaker 0: >> I don't see him.
Speaker 0: >> Okay, sir, I'm with my squad inside of Saks Fifth Avenue.
Speaker 0: Two under arrest.
Speaker 0: >> All right, two in custody there.
Speaker 0: >> Thousand bucks.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, shit.
Speaker 0: >> What's your record looking like?
Speaker 0: >> Not a good record.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah?
Speaker 0: >> Not anymore.
Speaker 0: >> What do you mean, good as in bad, or good as in good?
Speaker 0: >> This is what this man died for, so you guys can steal shit.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> You should be ashamed of yourself.
Speaker 0: >> There is no shame.
Speaker 0: >> Did this guy get patted down?
Speaker 0: >> Not by me.
Speaker 0: >> You guys, somebody pat him down?
Speaker 0: >> He did.
Speaker 0: That guy right there.
Speaker 0: That guy right there got him down.
Speaker 0: >> Brian.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> I just heard something.
Speaker 0: I just heard something.
Speaker 0: >> Ah!
Speaker 0: >> Nice, Matty.
Speaker 0: >> I'm on the car.
Speaker 0: >> Yep.
Speaker 0: >> We got a train coming.
Speaker 0: >> We need to shut down Ring Road.
Speaker 0: They're looting coffee bars, looting all of their cars on Ring Road.
Speaker 0: We need to shut down Ring Road.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, we need to shut down Ring Road as well.
Speaker 0: They're looting them all.
Speaker 0: >> Frank, this is Charlie One.
Speaker 0: Supposed to have some help coming in from Lennon over there.
Speaker 0: >> Check on that.
Speaker 0: We'll have them block Ring Road at Huntington.
Speaker 0: >> Okay, I'll get them.
Speaker 0: >> En route to the Delta, Charlie One.
Speaker 0: We're going to head up to that American area right now where all the cars are parked.
Speaker 0: >> Hello?
Speaker 0: Hello?
Speaker 0: >> I think that was security over there.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, yeah?
Speaker 0: >> Really?
Speaker 0: >> That might have been security.
Speaker 0: >> They're in the midst of it.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, we got held over.
Speaker 0: Should be time eight minutes ago.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, from days ago?
Speaker 0: >> First house.
Speaker 0: >> Do we have their names?
Speaker 0: >> Somebody want to copy them down so we can look in?
Speaker 0: >> Get on the fucking ground.
Speaker 0: Run in here.
Speaker 0: >> That's it.
Speaker 0: >> Get down.
Speaker 0: Get down.
Speaker 0: >> Fucking hands behind your back.
Speaker 0: Now.
Speaker 0: >> Shut your mouth.
Speaker 0: >> Shut up.
Speaker 0: >> I'm not talking to anybody.
Speaker 0: >> Put your hand behind your back.
Speaker 0: >> Your fucking hands behind your back.
Speaker 0: Now.
Speaker 0: >> Somebody get up there with him.
Speaker 0: >> He's got a trooper.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, really?
Speaker 0: >> Beanie.
Speaker 0: >> You got anything sharp on you?
Speaker 0: >> No, sir.
Speaker 0: >> Roll over.
Speaker 0: >> Where are you from?
Speaker 0: >> Boston, sir.
Speaker 0: >> Where?
Speaker 0: >> Here, Boston.
Speaker 0: >> Your name's going to be all over the paper.
Speaker 0: >> No, sir.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, yeah.
Speaker 0: >> Lowest of the low.
Speaker 0: >> Sir, no.
Speaker 0: >> I didn't do anything wrong.
Speaker 0: >> Please, sir.
Speaker 0: >> You can have some serious issues.
Speaker 0: >> Yes, sir.
Speaker 0: >> Roll back on your side.
Speaker 0: >> No weapons on you.
Speaker 0: >> No, sir.
Speaker 0: >> What's this?
Speaker 0: >> My phone, sir.
Speaker 0: >> Okay.
Speaker 0: >> Is somebody with the--?
Speaker 0: >> Can I get a--?
Speaker 0: >> Why don't you let him finish what he's doing?
Speaker 0: >> Yes, sir.
Speaker 0: >> If you didn't want to be on the ground, you wouldn't have broken in this place.
Speaker 0: >> Hello?
Speaker 0: Hello?
Speaker 0: >> What's going on?
Speaker 0: >> Hello?
Speaker 0: >> Come on in, bro.
Speaker 0: >> All right.
Speaker 0: I'm from the store.
Speaker 0: >> Okay.
Speaker 0: >> Hey, how's it going?
Speaker 0: >> How's it going?
Speaker 0: >> All right.
Speaker 0: >> How many we have over here now?
Speaker 0: >> One, two, three.
Speaker 0: >> We have four?
Speaker 0: Let's pick him up and get going.
Speaker 0: >> Over this way.
Speaker 0: >> Yes, sir.
Speaker 0: >> This will be our collection point down here.
Speaker 0: >> Who else wants to join the team here?
Speaker 0: >> Hey, welcome.
Speaker 0: >> Here you go.
Speaker 0: Lowest of the low.
Speaker 0: >> Good.
Speaker 0: You're going to sit down next to this gentleman.
Speaker 0: And you're not going to make a fucking noise, right?
Speaker 0: >> You got the other one?
Speaker 0: >> Izzy.
Speaker 0: Want to bring him back with the others?
Speaker 0: >> I'll bring him up front to this way.
Speaker 0: >> Okay.
Speaker 0: >> Stand up.
Speaker 0: >> I don't know if the transport's here.
Speaker 0: >> Which way are you going to bring him?
Speaker 0: >> Well, we're just collecting him back there.
Speaker 0: What if the transport's here?
Speaker 0: >> You hear me?
Speaker 0: >> No, I'm not listening to you.
Speaker 0: Shut your mouth.
Speaker 0: >> My blood circulation's cut.
Speaker 0: No.
Speaker 0: >> Okay.
Speaker 0: Don't break in and loot stores.
Speaker 0: >> I didn't loot anything.
Speaker 0: Can you please?
Speaker 0: Please, let me.
Speaker 0: Can you guys help me?
Speaker 0: Please.
Speaker 0: I'll get them off the me.
Speaker 0: My hands, they hurt though.
Speaker 0: I'm not trying to ask for the bag.
Speaker 0: >> Go join the party.
Speaker 0: >> Go sit right there.
Speaker 0: >> Please, can you help me with this?
Speaker 0: >> Thank you.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, my goodness.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, please.
Speaker 0: >> There's more?
Speaker 0: Can't get out that way, I don't think.
Speaker 0: [police radio chatter] [phone ringing].
Speaker 0: >> Delta, there's several arrests coming in off of this Boylston and Ring Road.
Speaker 0: >> Get on the fucking ground!
Speaker 0: All of you, get on the ground!
Speaker 0: >> The other two got away.
Speaker 0: >> You have any needles on you?
Speaker 0: >> You sure?
Speaker 0: >> Needles?
Speaker 0: >> I don't want to get poked.
Speaker 0: >> I don't know you.
Speaker 0: You're a fucking drug addict.
Speaker 0: You got a knife on you.
Speaker 0: >> Fucking loser.
Speaker 0: Hey.
Speaker 0: If they went all the way back, like that back hallway, can they get out?
Speaker 0: Okay.
Speaker 0: Just wanted to make sure they weren't still in there.
Speaker 0: [police radio chatter] >> The ship's charging federally.
Speaker 0: Domestic terrorism.
Speaker 0: Do a solid 20 down Leavenworth.
Speaker 0: The world's better off without you.
Speaker 0: [phone ringing].
Speaker 0: >> Right here.
Speaker 0: Ryan.
Speaker 0: Hello.
Speaker 0: We just got another one upstairs.
Speaker 0: Two others got away.
Speaker 0: We were clearing the upstairs.
Speaker 0: So that's five, I think, right?
Speaker 0: >> Yep.
Speaker 0: >> Water?
Speaker 0: >> We have them in the dressing room at Saks Fifth Avenue, Ring Road side.
Speaker 0: Okay.
Speaker 0: We're going to be moving them out.
Speaker 0: We got five now.
Speaker 0: >> Okay.
Speaker 0: >> Get them all out?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: [police radio chatter] >> Bring out like two at a time.
Speaker 0: [police radio chatter] >> Guys.
Speaker 0: Hands on this guy.
Speaker 0: >> Which one?
Speaker 0: Hold on.
Speaker 0: I got to put this shit on.
Speaker 0: >> We'll go three and then we'll take the other two.
Speaker 0: >> Take care of the first guy's phone and keys.
Speaker 0: >> Which, that guy?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: You want to stay in here with these guys?
Speaker 0: >> Yep.
Speaker 0: >> Ryan.
Speaker 0: Property for the first guy.
Speaker 0: >> That's mine.
Speaker 0: That's mine.
Speaker 0: >> This one's yours?
Speaker 0: Okay.
Speaker 0: [police radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> Just stop asking me questions, will you?
Speaker 0: >> Okay, but can I have my keys?
Speaker 0: >> No.
Speaker 0: This man already broke my phone.
Speaker 0: >> Look at this one.
Speaker 0: Look at this one.
Speaker 0: That shit's yours.
Speaker 0: [phone beeps].
Speaker 0: [police radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> Why don't you sit around so he can fix the cuff on this guy?
Speaker 0: >> That's not even loosened up at all.
Speaker 0: >> Why don't you say please and thank you?
Speaker 0: >> I already said please.
Speaker 0: Ask him.
Speaker 0: Multiple times.
Speaker 0: >> You want to get your mouth cracked?
Speaker 0: >> No, for real.
Speaker 0: >> Good?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, we can take the other tape.
Speaker 0: >> Yo, I've been handcuffed before, but that's not it.
Speaker 0: Like, this is not like that.
Speaker 0: Like, y'all tighten up that.
Speaker 0: Like, look.
Speaker 0: You see?
Speaker 0: I got a wound right there.
Speaker 0: It's not going off.
Speaker 0: Like, don't you see?
Speaker 0: right there?
Speaker 0: Right there.
Speaker 0: >> He's still loosening the cuff.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, that's what I'm asking.
Speaker 0: [police radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> I got no cuffs left.
Speaker 0: I'm sure I had zip cuffs.
Speaker 0: We can get some shoelaces out of the shoe department.
Speaker 0: [police radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> You're fucking unbelievable, man.
Speaker 0: You are almost like, you could be funny.
Speaker 0: Like a TV, you could be a comedian.
Speaker 0: >> All right.
Speaker 0: Come on.
Speaker 0: >> Keep it cool.
Speaker 0: >> I'm keeping it cool.
Speaker 0: >> Throwing out the way you came in.
Speaker 0: Throwing out this way, right?
Speaker 0: [police radio chatter] >> All right.
Speaker 0: Watch your head.
Speaker 0: Go ahead.
Speaker 0: >> I got bad news.
Speaker 0: >> Come on, dude.
Speaker 0: Do you want to stay in here all night?
Speaker 0: >> I'm not lying.
Speaker 0: >> Just wait right there.
Speaker 0: >> Watch out for this thing.
Speaker 0: You got it.
Speaker 0: >> What's your name, officer?
Speaker 0: >> Kaslan, H-A-S-L-A-T-T-23-0-8-6-50-F.
Speaker 0: >> Okay, you don't have to-- Yo, you don't have to keep pushing me like that.
Speaker 0: >> I'm not pushing you.
Speaker 0: >> No, I'm not.
Speaker 0: I didn't get nothing.
Speaker 0: I don't know what you're talking about.
Speaker 0: [police radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> I put his phone back in his pocket.
Speaker 0: >> I don't got any cuffs.
Speaker 0: [police radio chatter] >> Boston!
Speaker 0: >> Only the ones that can't run.
Speaker 0: [laughter] >> You know damn well.
Speaker 0: I can't run, nigga!
Speaker 0: I got you in my titties, nigga!
Speaker 0: [laughter] >> I know!
Speaker 0: I know!
Speaker 0: Bullshit!
Speaker 0: I didn't even-- My man just didn't drive fast enough.
Speaker 0: >> Yo, dog!
Speaker 0: >> I seen the girl with the rubber bullets in her face.
Speaker 0: That shit would hurt.
Speaker 0: [laughter] >> You're shaking your head at me.
Speaker 0: You're shaking your head at me.
Speaker 0: [police radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> You and everybody else, my friend.
Speaker 0: >> I don't care what you do.
Speaker 0: >> That's why I tried to get into Boston.
Speaker 0: I had water in there.
Speaker 0: Yo!
Speaker 0: Yo, what is it?
Speaker 0: >> 650. >>
Speaker 0: Yep.
Speaker 0: >> My boyfriend, he was just reporting, and I don't know why he's in the paddy wagon.
Speaker 0: He was just reporting.
Speaker 0: I'm a nurse from the National Guard.
Speaker 0: I don't know who he is.
Speaker 0: There's about ten people in there.
Speaker 0: >> What's this?
Speaker 0: >> Not yours.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, should I arrest the motherfucker or not?
Speaker 0: Oh, oh, okay.
Speaker 0: Oh, what'd you say?
Speaker 0: All right.
Speaker 0: Should I do it or not?
Speaker 0: Like, what the fuck is going on?
Speaker 0: What the fuck is going on?
Speaker 0: Oh, that's what I said.
Speaker 0: Oh, should I arrest this motherfucker or not?
Speaker 0: Oh, not so fast.
Speaker 0: All right, well, I'm the only one out here, bro.
Speaker 0: Damn.
Speaker 0: >> It's all B&E.
Speaker 0: It's all from SACS team.
Speaker 0: It's all Officer Almeida's arrest.
Speaker 0: It's all my fucking--.
Speaker 0: >> All right.
Speaker 0: Oh, they are.
Speaker 0: Where the fuck did you guys pick your prison?
Speaker 0: That wagon over there.
Speaker 0: That wagon's down there turning around.
Speaker 0: >> Okay, all right.
Speaker 0: Just forgot.
Speaker 0: Thanks, guys.
Speaker 0: >> All the same report?
Speaker 0: >> Too bad.
Speaker 0: >> And I got a detour in the morning.
Speaker 0: >> Who's seen you?
Speaker 0: >> What?
Speaker 0: >> You got to help me with the court package.
Speaker 0: I don't know how to do the court package.
Speaker 0: >> I'll book it right.
Speaker 0: >> I'm on my last night on.
Speaker 0: >> All this shit's going to be fucking squashed anyway.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, yeah.
Speaker 0: Oh, no.
Speaker 0: This is not going to be war and peace.
Speaker 0: >> It's going to be.
Speaker 0: these fucking people were found inside Lord and Taylor's.
Speaker 0: >> Actually, with a mass arrest.
Speaker 0: Isn't a supervisor supposed to write it?
Speaker 0: >> I don't know.
Speaker 0: We go find the captain.
Speaker 0: >> Mass arrest.
Speaker 0: I think supervisor's not supposed to write it.
Speaker 0: >> The kid that went down the wrong way and came back, I knew I really had to go down there, so that door was fucking closed.
Speaker 0: So I just kept coming full speed.
Speaker 0: Like, as long as Taylor unblocked, I just fucking hammered the fuck out of him.
Speaker 0: >> Dude, I've never seen anything like this in 10 years.
Speaker 0: We're fucking guns out clearing Saks Fifth Avenue.
Speaker 0: Like, people running.
Speaker 0: That was wild, dude.
Speaker 0: >> The commissioner, the mayor, and the--.
Speaker 0: >> They're going to say it was a peaceful protest.
Speaker 0: >> It's fucking crazy, dude.
Speaker 0: [police siren].
Speaker 0: >> You guys want to continue our fucking walk through the mall?
Speaker 0: You troopers want to take any arrests tonight?
Speaker 0: >> Hey, does anybody have a pair of flex cuffs?
Speaker 0: 'Cause I don't have any cuffs.
Speaker 0: >> I got one set of cuffs that are as easy, so I don't mind if I lose 'em.
Speaker 0: >> Where's McGrail?
Speaker 0: >> You guys want water?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, a case of water, man.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, grab me one, Billy.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Speaker 0: >> He ain't down here.
Speaker 0: >> McGrail walked down here.
Speaker 0: He said to continue on.
Speaker 0: McGrail's a fast walker.
Speaker 0: I thought we were following you guys.
Speaker 0: I thought you guys were following him.
Speaker 0: You guys working the first half already?
Speaker 0: >> Going up.
Speaker 0: >> Hazlitt's on 7.
Speaker 0: Hazlitt's on 7.
Speaker 0: Oh, thank you, man.
Speaker 0: >> Hey.
Speaker 0: >> We thought you already walked off, so we're a little further down by the parking garage entrance where the troopers' cars are parked.
Speaker 0: >> We'll wait here.
Speaker 0: >> I have a wagon coming for you.
Speaker 0: >> Where's he at?
Speaker 0: >> He's up there.
Speaker 0: He said this way here.
Speaker 0: He's coming.
Speaker 0: >> Where's the side street?
Speaker 0: >> He's up there.
Speaker 0: You guys started walking down.
Speaker 0: I thought you guys... >> Anybody at the Copley Mall still?
Speaker 0: We're getting alarms and people trying to break in the stores in the mall.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, is it?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> Sir, we got some assets from the police metro heading up there.
Speaker 0: >> All right.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> I'll have to kiss if I have one.
Speaker 0: >> Okay, very good.
Speaker 0: >> Fuckin' beat.
Speaker 0: [horn honks].
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> 'Cause the state police was supposed to be up there with a squad.
Speaker 0: >> Okay, I don't see anybody there.
Speaker 0: We got traffic coming up on Boylston.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, you see four?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, I got a couple of Chelsea officers here.
Speaker 0: [horn honks].
Speaker 0: >> They'll check and see if there's another street open head over.
Speaker 0: >> Super, if they can block the traffic coming up on Boylston, that'd be great.
Speaker 0: >> Get out.
Speaker 0: You're so stupid doing that.
Speaker 0: >> Block traffic coming up on Boylston from Dalton.
Speaker 0: >> What are we doing?
Speaker 0: Waiting for the captain to tell me what the hell he wanted, and then he just bonded off.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> Was yours the one they were talking about?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, sir.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> There's no need to be.
Speaker 0: >> You see the cruiser in the alley?
Speaker 0: That was your cruiser, right?
Speaker 0: >> Jesus.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter] [laughter].
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, what the fuck?
Speaker 0: This is wild.
Speaker 0: >> Say it again.
Speaker 0: >> This is fucking wild.
Speaker 0: We're fucking inside sacks, and we're fighting with two of them, and then more of them start breaking in the fucking place.
Speaker 0: They're running around the upstairs.
Speaker 0: It's insane.
Speaker 0: It's like a fucking war zone.
Speaker 0: >> Yes.
Speaker 0: Five of the summits.
Speaker 0: >> One of the kids ran out, and he jumped off the side.
Speaker 0: >> As patrolmen, we were just wondering, isn't a supervisor supposed to write mass arrests?
Speaker 0: >> That's why I came today.
Speaker 0: [laughter] >> Just, you know, just trying to throw a little--.
Speaker 0: >> This is not a mass arrest.
Speaker 0: They're all separate 1-1s, so enjoy.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, this is a 1-1-1, right?
Speaker 0: >> I've got to say, none of that-- Hey, that was my knee.
Speaker 0: I was getting ready to go outside with my knee right now, so he said separate 1 with my knee.
Speaker 0: >> Fucking back is on fire.
Speaker 0: >> Only guy making sense this evening.
Speaker 0: Only guy making sense.
Speaker 0: The only guy making sense this evening.
Speaker 0: >> You guys got guys from crack scene out here filming everything, too?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> I've had this thing on the whole fucking time.
Speaker 0: >> You have, yeah.
Speaker 0: >> Wouldn't they--.
Speaker 0: >> Since they--.
Speaker 0: >> It hasn't run out of battery?
Speaker 0: >> No, I think we get 16 hours.
Speaker 0: >> I don't think that one.
Speaker 0: It seems to not affect the battery, whether it's recording or not.
Speaker 0: Because yesterday-- Not yesterday, I banged in, but Friday, I had a four-hour recording because they rioted over at the station.
Speaker 0: And the battery was still at, like, 47% or something.
Speaker 0: >> All right.
Speaker 0: >> Everyone down there, I guess.
Speaker 0: >> It's good for shit like this.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, I'm saying that's like a fucking 200-voice.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> Is looting a charge?
Speaker 0: >> I would, like, trespass--.
Speaker 0: >> Disorderly.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, I'll take one, thanks.
Speaker 0: >> Thank you.
Speaker 0: >> Put it together for you.
Speaker 0: >> Delta Charlie
Speaker 0: 1. >>
Speaker 0: Charlie
Speaker 0: Delta Charlie 1, you calling?
Speaker 0: >> Why is this idiot so soft there?
Speaker 0: >> Belmont?
Speaker 0: >> Like, what the fuck?
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> Okay, everybody's heading up the Newberry Street.
Speaker 0: >> Is that good?
Speaker 0: >> We can go get another five.
Speaker 0: >> Out.
Speaker 0: >> I didn't think to grab him when he left.
Speaker 0: >> Thanks, man.
Speaker 0: >> We'll try to raise them on you.
Speaker 0: They may be on one.
Speaker 0: >> Where are you right now?
Speaker 0: We'll meet up with you or another location.
Speaker 0: >> Awesome, thank you.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> These guys still haven't finished.
Speaker 0: >> You guys want to cross?
Speaker 0: >> If you want to do such.
Speaker 0: >> Hey, buddy.
Speaker 0: >> You got me.
Speaker 0: >> Hey!
Speaker 0: >> Did you have fun?
Speaker 0: >> What's up, sweetie?
Speaker 0: >> This is, like, fucking insane, dude.
Speaker 0: We were just chasing them all around inside of Saks Fifth Avenue.
Speaker 0: As we're locking them up, there's more coming in.
Speaker 0: Fucking... >> How many did you arrest so far?
Speaker 0: >> Six.
Speaker 0: >> Jesus.
Speaker 0: Did anybody try to fight you guys up at all?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, they were whipping fucking bottles.
Speaker 0: The guys downtown got fucked.
Speaker 0: >> Thank you.
Speaker 0: >> They got hit hard downtown.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, yeah?
Speaker 0: Well, I mean, we were just close up.
Speaker 0: We got guys all down the street, but there's guys, Adidas is all blown out and everything else.
Speaker 0: You should see our cruiser.
Speaker 0: They smashed it right in front of us.
Speaker 0: And then they fucking broke into a place and lit it on fire.
Speaker 0: It's a store.
Speaker 0: It's a Zara store.
Speaker 0: It sells clothes for, like, fucking European men.
Speaker 0: >> That's crazy.
Speaker 0: >> All right.
Speaker 0: I got to go catch up with them.
Speaker 0: >> All right, brother.
Speaker 0: Be safe.
Speaker 0: >> Probably see you around.
Speaker 0: >> All right, brother.
Speaker 0: Be safe.
Speaker 0: >> It's my car, Sergeant.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, yeah?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: I'm supposed to... When you got activated, I was like, "I'm not
Speaker 0: coming.".
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, I'm already here.
Speaker 0: >> Not that I'm aware of, but we still had it open.
Speaker 0: >> It'd be funny if the guy just kept on going.
Speaker 0: >> Fuck you!
Speaker 0: >> Common, Clarendon, Common, Fairfield, Common, Gloucester.
Speaker 0: Hoopery and Exeter.
Speaker 0: >> What the hell are you talking about?
Speaker 0: >> I thought this was a state house over there.
Speaker 0: >> If anybody actually thought they were going to a fucking state house, I mean, come on.
Speaker 0: >> Like, how did we, you know what I mean?
Speaker 0: >> Like, it's played out in different cities before it happened here, like... >> To me, it just seemed like when you got here, it was when you stopped, you know what I mean?
Speaker 0: The movement just stopped.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> You parked it here.
Speaker 0: >> What's up?
Speaker 0: >> Oh, yeah.
Speaker 0: >> This is mine.
Speaker 0: >> Thank you for your service.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: When did you guys get here?
Speaker 0: >> 20 minutes ago.
Speaker 0: >> This is fucking wild, dude.
Speaker 0: >> You've been going all day?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> No time to stop.
Speaker 0: >> Did you get ordered in?
Speaker 0: >> No, this is my regular... Well, now I'm going overtime.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, it's even worse.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, all the guys are going now.
Speaker 0: >> We were like... We were inside Saks Fifth Avenue.
Speaker 0: They're fucking in there looting.
Speaker 0: We've locked up two.
Speaker 0: More of them fucking break in while we're fucking standing right there.
Speaker 0: Take another two.
Speaker 0: Go upstairs.
Speaker 0: There's three of them.
Speaker 0: Like, hands full of shit.
Speaker 0: I fucking gun-faced them.
Speaker 0: Two of them got away.
Speaker 0: We got one.
Speaker 0: >> Holy shit.
Speaker 0: >> They were doing it right in front of us.
Speaker 0: You should see their cruises.
Speaker 0: >> It's going to happen tomorrow, too.
Speaker 0: Didn't they burn two of your cars?
Speaker 0: >> I don't know if they burned them.
Speaker 0: Not here.
Speaker 0: They're fucking ruined.
Speaker 0: They're in an alley.
Speaker 0: One of these alleys.
Speaker 0: >> Holy shit.
Speaker 0: >> You know a place where we can take a piss?
Speaker 0: For real.
Speaker 0: >> I'm not going in the alley.
Speaker 0: >> You know how many fucking people were in that alley running away every time I fucking poked my head down there?
Speaker 0: >> Nothing's open.
Speaker 0: >> I don't feel like getting assaulted by those fucking... Look at those pork chops.
Speaker 0: Holy shit.
Speaker 0: >> I haven't gotten a haircut in three months.
Speaker 0: >> Dude, you're a fucking '70s porn star.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, yeah.
Speaker 0: I like it.
Speaker 0: >> That is amazing.
Speaker 0: >> What?
Speaker 0: >> The camera.
Speaker 0: >> That's okay.
Speaker 0: That's amazing.
Speaker 0: I love it.
Speaker 0: You do it great.
Speaker 0: >> Fucking one-way street.
Speaker 0: >> This is great.
Speaker 0: >> So it's going to be tomorrow, too?
Speaker 0: >> I'll be off.
Speaker 0: Fuck this place.
Speaker 0: >> You'll be here.
Speaker 0: >> No, no, no, no, no.
Speaker 0: >> No tomorrow.
Speaker 0: >> We were building security at the station because on Friday they came and it was not good.
Speaker 0: And then they were acting up down at Common and they had us get in a fucking van and drive to Newbury Street.
Speaker 0: And it was complete and utter chaos and lawlessness.
Speaker 0: They smashed a cruiser literally that far away from me.
Speaker 0: They broke into a building, lit it on fire while we were just standing there.
Speaker 0: Fucking insanity.
Speaker 0: There was only, like, eight of us.
Speaker 0: >> No, he's fooling around.
Speaker 0: Yeah, I think he's with a canner.
Speaker 0: >> No, he's cheating.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, nice.
Speaker 0: Awesome.
Speaker 0: >> All right.
Speaker 0: I figured I'd try.
Speaker 0: If you see him, we'll be around.
Speaker 0: >> Absolutely.
Speaker 0: Absolutely.
Speaker 0: >> You're not supposed to be with us, man.
Speaker 0: We're here to fight wars.
Speaker 0: >> 903, are you mobile, Sergeant?
Speaker 0: >> I want to shoot myself in the fucking head.
Speaker 0: >> I have a supervisor on the air with wheels at this time.
Speaker 0: >> Can you make it?
Speaker 0: >> I think he's still on the way.
Speaker 0: >> I'm pretending it was them mostly.
Speaker 0: They're actually pretty decent.
Speaker 0: >> He's like 12 years old.
Speaker 0: >> Really?
Speaker 0: >> Shut that down.
Speaker 0: He's a bomb.
Speaker 0: Somebody hit him.
Speaker 0: >> All right, you have that.
Speaker 0: We'll be doing a loop.
Speaker 0: >> Good work.
Speaker 0: You're safe.
Speaker 0: >> You could actually probably take a leak and just go in one of the buildings that got looted.
Speaker 0: I'm serious.
Speaker 0: Find an employee bathroom or something.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, but I don't want to go walking through there with cameras and all that.
Speaker 0: >> I don't think anything's actually open.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, but I don't want to be walking through in that.
Speaker 0: >> I got to go.
Speaker 0: Be safe.
Speaker 0: >> Watch yourself, son.
Speaker 0: Keep moving.
Speaker 0: >> Where are we going?
Speaker 0: >> We're going to take a stroll through the coffee mall.
Speaker 0: >> I'm broke from Columbus.
Speaker 0: That was the lift.
Speaker 0: >> I can't wait.
Speaker 0: I'm filling out a form 25 on my cruiser when I get there.
Speaker 0: >> Like you just parked where it's damaged.
Speaker 0: >> We've got a group of people going right into sites again.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, boy.
Speaker 0: >> Here we go.
Speaker 0: >> This is our specialty.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, my ass.
Speaker 0: >> Get down!
Speaker 0: >> Coming back.
Speaker 0: >> We're going upstairs.
Speaker 0: >> You guys good?
Speaker 0: >> Get the fuck down!
Speaker 0: >> We're trying to get back.
Speaker 0: >> Take the bag off.
Speaker 0: >> We need a couple more units on Ring Road.
Speaker 0: >> Stay here.
Speaker 0: Don't move.
Speaker 0: >> What?
Speaker 0: >> Go ahead.
Speaker 0: >> Sit up if you want.
Speaker 0: >> Ryan, I got one here.
Speaker 0: >> All right.
Speaker 0: >> We going to the trussing room?
Speaker 0: >> Yep.
Speaker 0: >> Stand up.
Speaker 0: You ready?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> Just roll onto your knee, okay?
Speaker 0: >> No, no, I got it.
Speaker 0: >> Okay.
Speaker 0: >> Thank you.
Speaker 0: >> Can you pat him down?
Speaker 0: >> I'll do it when we get back down.
Speaker 0: >> We need Ring Road for three more transports.
Speaker 0: Again, remember, the males are going up there.
Speaker 0: You need a female for six.
Speaker 0: >> We've got to wait for the wagon, so they can... >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> Got anything on you?
Speaker 0: Knives, guns, needles?
Speaker 0: If I get stuck, you're going to the hospital, too.
Speaker 0: >> Okay.
Speaker 0: >> What's this?
Speaker 0: >> I don't know.
Speaker 0: >> Come in there.
Speaker 0: >> Come and sit.
Speaker 0: >> Last I heard was Herford and Newberry.
Speaker 0: Let me check with Stacy.
Speaker 0: >> Sit down, please.
Speaker 0: >> ...towards Mass Dab on Newberry Street.
Speaker 0: There were three mobile troopers that were not assigned elsewhere that came down to join them, so they had a pretty good number of officers that were moving that group along.
Speaker 0: >> Huh?
Speaker 0: >> Just got a report.
Speaker 0: that group moved in Newberry and Mass Dab and now are breaking into Urban Outfitters.
Speaker 0: Newberry and Mass Dab breaking into Urban Outfitters.
Speaker 0: >> Probably four.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, those spike locks that I had, they were actually holding a bomber down here, so... Is there anyone else that could move up to that group?
Speaker 0: >> Try it.
Speaker 0: >> Hello?
Speaker 0: >> The other one had three locked doors.
Speaker 0: >> The group is now moving towards Calm and Mass Dab.
Speaker 0: Calm and Mass Dab, they're moving on.
Speaker 0: >> There's probably more of them upstairs.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> I'll pick you up and I'll see you on QT4.
Speaker 0: >> Gentlemen, the store's closed.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, bring the dog in.
Speaker 0: >> This fucking helmet, too.
Speaker 0: >> Hold on a second.
Speaker 0: >> They might have gone out the back.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, yeah, Snowberry, what do you need?
Speaker 0: >> Head towards Newberry and Mass Dab for a look at that group.
Speaker 0: >> Uh... >> They ran out last time that way.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, Charlie
Speaker 0: 4. >>
Speaker 0: All right, so we're going to try on this post for you.
Speaker 0: What else, Tom?
Speaker 0: >> Uh, Dartmouth and St.
Speaker 0: James.
Speaker 0: You'll probably need at least two cruisers at Dartmouth and St.
Speaker 0: I know you have reports of people trying to break into the CBS at 285 Columbus.
Speaker 0: At 285 Columbus, CBS is getting looted right now.
Speaker 0: >> This is where they went out the exit.
Speaker 0: >> Nope.
Speaker 0: >> QT4.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, just saw movement, right?
Speaker 0: >> Back there.
Speaker 0: >> They must have gone down.
Speaker 0: >> Get on the fucking ground!
Speaker 0: >> On the ground, now!
Speaker 0: >> Get on the ground, you're going to get shot!
Speaker 0: >> Get the fuck down!
Speaker 0: Down!
Speaker 0: Put your hands behind your back.
Speaker 0: Stay on your stomach.
Speaker 0: >> I don't have cuffs.
Speaker 0: >> Watch the stairs, Matt.
Speaker 0: Okay, sir, do you have any weapons on you?
Speaker 0: >> No, sir.
Speaker 0: >> Roll on your side, I'm just going to check you, okay?
Speaker 0: >> Okay.
Speaker 0: >> Jewel.
Speaker 0: >> What flavor is it?
Speaker 0: Give it to me.
Speaker 0: >> All right, sir, roll up onto your knee.
Speaker 0: No, come on.
Speaker 0: Put your knee in front.
Speaker 0: Yeah, there you go.
Speaker 0: Step up.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> It's going to be nice for you if the annoying shit-fucking-idiot does, all right?
Speaker 0: >> Okay.
Speaker 0: >> Going downstairs, you are obviously under arrest.
Speaker 0: >> I think I dropped my phone.
Speaker 0: >> You want to help me get it out, please?
Speaker 0: >> No, go ahead.
Speaker 0: >> I'm not looking around the store for that.
Speaker 0: I've got other people in here fucking stealing shit.
Speaker 0: I don't want somebody to run behind us.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, well, that's unfortunate.
Speaker 0: You can tell that to the judge later.
Speaker 0: >> Coming in with one!
Speaker 0: Got another one upstairs.
Speaker 0: Still wandering around up there.
Speaker 0: >> How many more up there?
Speaker 0: >> I don't know, but I'm out of cuffs.
Speaker 0: How about you guys?
Speaker 0: >> I got one.
Speaker 0: >> What's your name, sir?
Speaker 0: >> Josh.
Speaker 0: >> Okay, can Josh come back here?
Speaker 0: >> You guys.
Speaker 0: >> Two more up there?
Speaker 0: >> Huh?
Speaker 0: >> Two more up?
Speaker 0: >> At least one.
Speaker 0: >> You guys have cuffs?
Speaker 0: >> They got a flex cuff.
Speaker 0: >> Okay.
Speaker 0: Let's bring this guy back, too.
Speaker 0: >> Can you get up?
Speaker 0: Get up.
Speaker 0: >> I'm going to try.
Speaker 0: You can help me up, please.
Speaker 0: >> One, two, three.
Speaker 0: >> What do you want?
Speaker 0: >> I don't want to lose it.
Speaker 0: >> Give it to me.
Speaker 0: I'll put it in your pocket.
Speaker 0: >> Thank you, brother.
Speaker 0: I appreciate it.
Speaker 0: This shit's stressful.
Speaker 0: >> For you?
Speaker 0: >> How's your day?
Speaker 0: What time you started today?
Speaker 0: >> Four o'clock.
Speaker 0: We dealt with this shit Friday night, too.
Speaker 0: It's old.
Speaker 0: >> We'll be done with you, okay?
Speaker 0: But as of right now, you're under arrest.
Speaker 0: >> Come on.
Speaker 0: Is there anybody in that room?
Speaker 0: >> I've got one here, so you can throw him in there.
Speaker 0: >> Let's go to that third room.
Speaker 0: Ew, what the fuck?
Speaker 0: Go ahead, have a seat.
Speaker 0: >> I'm going to go join them upstairs.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, are you good down here?
Speaker 0: >> Let's keep one more down here, Josh.
Speaker 0: >> Go ahead.
Speaker 0: >> Call from the public alley 430.
Speaker 0: Got a report of a guy breaking into someone's home there.
Speaker 0: >> Joshua?
Speaker 0: >> Public alley 430.
Speaker 0: Man with a black backpack looking at broken windows.
Speaker 0: >> What's out of
Speaker 0: 430? >>
Speaker 0: Delta Alpha 81 on channel
Speaker 0: 5. >>
Speaker 0: Delta Alpha
Speaker 0: 81. >>
Speaker 0: I need at least a D4 detective to come down here and take a photograph.
Speaker 0: I just got this.
Speaker 0: CPS was just looted at Clarendon in Columbus.
Speaker 0: We have three under arrest.
Speaker 0: >> Under arrest at Clarendon in Columbus.
Speaker 0: Any D4 detectives?
Speaker 0: >> We have a service unit down here, too.
Speaker 0: We're going to have to protect this senior.
Speaker 0: >> Is that yours?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> Delta Alpha
Speaker 0: 81. >>
Speaker 0: Is that your gun?
Speaker 0: >> I think so.
Speaker 0: >> Is it?
Speaker 0: If Officer Golinas is on the air, can he answer up for me?
Speaker 0: >> Steiner.
Speaker 0: >> Gagnon, where are you guys going?
Speaker 0: >> Guy inside a UDT, kicking the door down right now.
Speaker 0: He must be trapped inside.
Speaker 0: >> Delta, please go to 7.
Speaker 0: I need a tow.
Speaker 0: >> Delta Base, hold on.
Speaker 0: >> Delta
Speaker 0: 82. >>
Speaker 0: You can't cry, bro.
Speaker 0: >> 822. >>
Speaker 0: You can't even cry.
Speaker 0: >> Yes, sir.
Speaker 0: Location, where are we going?
Speaker 0: >> EAS.
Speaker 0: >> It's going to be the CVS on Columbus in Clarendon.
Speaker 0: >> We have that, sir.
Speaker 0: >> Delta Alpha 2D, need transport as well.
Speaker 0: >> Guys, somebody's got to keep that plaza street shut down.
Speaker 0: All the cars are coming up now.
Speaker 0: >> I can't take those plastic ones off.
Speaker 0: You have to cut them off, and you have to use special scissors.
Speaker 0: >> Delta Alpha 81, where are the prisoners going?
Speaker 0: Sergeant Rodriguez, see if you can send two more guys back to that cluster post.
Speaker 0: All those cars are coming right back up.
Speaker 0: I'll send them up there.
Speaker 0: We're just securing two right now, 888 Wilson.
Speaker 0: >> There's at least one other.
Speaker 0: How many were you up there with?
Speaker 0: How many people were you up there with?
Speaker 0: >> I came by myself, brother.
Speaker 0: >> No, it was you then, right?
Speaker 0: That I cuffed up there?
Speaker 0: Were you up there with somebody else?
Speaker 0: Just one guy.
Speaker 0: I just want to know how many people are still up there.
Speaker 0: >> Charlie 1, was there an announcement made on Channel 1 about officers doing a day tour tomorrow?
Speaker 0: That we're going to get on Channel
Speaker 0: 5? >>
Speaker 0: You want me to just shove this shit in their pockets?
Speaker 0: >> Yes, Timber.
Speaker 0: Let me clarify.
Speaker 0: I'll get back to you.
Speaker 0: >> I'll take it.
Speaker 0: >> Thank you.
Speaker 0: >> I'll give it to the guy right... >> I put a... Just like a fucking red line so you can read it.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, that's fine.
Speaker 0: >> You can read my shit again right now.
Speaker 0: >> Delta Charlie
Speaker 0: 1. >>
Speaker 0: Deshawn Ward.
Speaker 0: That sounds familiar.
Speaker 0: >> Officers that are supposed to be in for the day tour were told to talk to all the supervisors.
Speaker 0: That's all we have so far.
Speaker 0: >> I'm going to change my uniform.
Speaker 0: >> Yes, up to the supervisor.
Speaker 0: >> Got it.
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 0: >> This is Channel 5 for me.
Speaker 0: And I have the officers check with their supervisors and let me know... >> When you get booked, yeah.
Speaker 0: >> ...the locations they're at and we'll have some of these outside units assisted.
Speaker 0: >> Okay, all officers that are coming in for the day tour tomorrow, check with your supervisors about your staffing.
Speaker 0: And then supervisors, let Delta Charlie 1 know.
Speaker 0: >> It's already fucking 9 o'clock, man.
Speaker 0: >> Jesus.
Speaker 0: >> So we're waiting for transport now?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> We don't have any bus.
Speaker 0: >> That's the second time I've run out tonight.
Speaker 0: A lot of motherfuckers be acting the fool.
Speaker 0: It's a shame to use a tragedy like that for this.
Speaker 0: An excuse to go looting.
Speaker 0: Some man lost his life.
Speaker 0: Shameful shit.
Speaker 0: Obviously, you guys don't even care about the guy, right?
Speaker 0: I don't know where it is in this place, man.
Speaker 0: They're going to arraign you by phone.
Speaker 0: And then you'll make bail.
Speaker 0: It'll probably be like $40 because this county's a joke.
Speaker 0: >> What'd you say, bro?
Speaker 0: >> What?
Speaker 0: >> You said the bill would be like
Speaker 0: $40? >>
Speaker 0: I don't set it, but that's... >> All right, well, we're going to get you transported, so we'll get you out of here.
Speaker 0: >> Delta 9-3.
Speaker 0: >> We've got a form monitor at Saks Fifth Avenue.
Speaker 0: Ring right back.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, these four.
Speaker 0: >> Four more in the custody.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, so we're just looking for a transport.
Speaker 0: We're going to get them all out of here.
Speaker 0: >> Delta 4-2-5, what's that message?
Speaker 0: >> We need a transport.
Speaker 0: >> You from Boston?
Speaker 0: >> 2-5, can you transport this from Saks Fifth Avenue?
Speaker 0: >> We've got four more.
Speaker 0: >> At least that's the ending.
Speaker 0: >> Where are you from?
Speaker 0: >> Travis.
Speaker 0: >> You guys weren't here at Saks Fifth Avenue?
Speaker 0: >> That's fucked up.
Speaker 0: >> Where is he from?
Speaker 0: >> Who is this guy?
Speaker 0: >> You from around here?
Speaker 0: >> Right now, you guys are just going to get transported, and we'll probably be out of here quickly.
Speaker 0: >> Hello, this is Delta Charlie 1.
Speaker 0: Can you give me your location?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, you'll get there, you'll get booked, and then you don't have to come back.
Speaker 0: >> We're not even sure yet.
Speaker 0: The transportation is going to be filled out, so you're going to have to go on the other side of the city.
Speaker 0: >> Hey, how are you?
Speaker 0: >> You think I'm fucking blind?
Speaker 0: >> You think we're going to be five people in the rest of the city?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, we can't bail you, though.
Speaker 0: That's a bail magistrate.
Speaker 0: >> I can't.
Speaker 0: >> Well, you can.
Speaker 0: Come down.
Speaker 0: But first, you've got to get booked.
Speaker 0: >> Then the bail magistrate has to come, and then you've got to give him the money.
Speaker 0: >> It's a long process.
Speaker 0: It's a long process.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, how about everybody else?
Speaker 0: You guys want to go, too?
Speaker 0: You want to go?
Speaker 0: >> I want to fucking go.
Speaker 0: >> We're going to do that.
Speaker 0: >> Look, if you get a job and buy this stuff, you're going to get in trouble.
Speaker 0: >> I wish I would get fired.
Speaker 0: This job sucks.
Speaker 0: >> If you get a job and buy this stuff, how would that work?
Speaker 0: >> Oh, yeah.
Speaker 0: Did you find him?
Speaker 0: >> He might have got out, too.
Speaker 0: I mean, who knows?
Speaker 0: He could have fucking snuck down and got out, too.
Speaker 0: >> 903, we do have four to go.
Speaker 0: >> The one idiot actually fucking got down when I told him I was going to shoot him.
Speaker 0: >> The other guy booked it.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, this guy had to drive down, and he went into the fucking closet.
Speaker 0: >> Luckily, the key was sitting right at the door.
Speaker 0: >> That was good.
Speaker 0: I heard that.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: You should get a pair of corduroys.
Speaker 0: >> Looks good.
Speaker 0: >> I don't think they even have price tags on their clothes here.
Speaker 0: >> Fuck yeah.
Speaker 0: >> This is so outrageous.
Speaker 0: >> All right.
Speaker 0: That's good.
Speaker 0: You should roll with that.
Speaker 0: >> That's fucking amazing.
Speaker 0: >> I think we're all out of cuffs.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: We've got one more.
Speaker 0: >> Can we bring out a mannequin?
Speaker 0: >> That would be funny.
Speaker 0: >> I can get a girlfriend here.
Speaker 0: >> The troopers gave me the rustiest cuff in the state police.
Speaker 0: >> I have to put these on anybody.
Speaker 0: You know what I mean?
Speaker 0: >> Sorry, dude.
Speaker 0: That's why I live by you.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, shit.
Speaker 0: >> Who cares?
Speaker 0: >> He can take your cruiser, Brian.
Speaker 0: >> My car's total.
Speaker 0: >> You guys don't have cruisers?
Speaker 0: >> They fucking smash them right in front of us.
Speaker 0: >> So what we're going to do is once we get these guys transported, we'll go merge in with somebody else and we'll get you right back to the station.
Speaker 0: >> I'm going to fill out my slip tomorrow.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> It's a two-liner.
Speaker 0: >> And they have to go through three different doors.
Speaker 0: >> Are you just on the first half?
Speaker 0: >> Anybody?
Speaker 0: >> I want to go home, dude.
Speaker 0: >> So don't I.
Speaker 0: >> This sucks.
Speaker 0: >> But look at it this way.
Speaker 0: You can go do the two separate reports, fucking three lines each, and then fucking.
Speaker 0: just stay off the air.
Speaker 0: And I'll go merge up with somebody else.
Speaker 0: And then the two of you are out of here.
Speaker 0: I mean, there's reports.
Speaker 0: We'll take your fucking... >> Isn't it all one report?
Speaker 0: >> No, we'll do the two different reports for sacks, because it's two totally different times.
Speaker 0: >> Right, but five and five... >> Five.
Speaker 0: >> So it's four now, right?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, so we've got four now, so it'll be two reports.
Speaker 0: Four in one report, and five in the first report.
Speaker 0: >> I still have to summons the other guy.
Speaker 0: The Ward and Taylor guy.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, right.
Speaker 0: Do you really?
Speaker 0: >> No.
Speaker 0: >> I mean, the summons can wait a couple days.
Speaker 0: It's nothing urgent there.
Speaker 0: >> Where are they even going?
Speaker 0: >> I didn't get any shots in.
Speaker 0: >> Where are they going?
Speaker 0: >> We don't know yet.
Speaker 0: >> How can you even write the one-one?
Speaker 0: You can't start it until they're booked.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, yeah.
Speaker 0: At least we'll have to find out when they're booked.
Speaker 0: >> It's going to be hours, probably, because every place is filled.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> It would probably be beneficial to have him do it if he's coming in the morning, because then they'll all be done by then.
Speaker 0: We'll see where they're going, what the line's looking like, and where the other guys went.
Speaker 0: Do we know where they went?
Speaker 0: >> Who?
Speaker 0: Like Mike and stuff?
Speaker 0: Or the prisoners?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah, the first group.
Speaker 0: >> I think they went to four.
Speaker 0: >> Shut up, Abishai.
Speaker 0: There's probably fucking 15 phones littered around this place.
Speaker 0: >> Can I get my phone?
Speaker 0: >> No.
Speaker 0: >> I was freezing earlier, and now I'm running around this motherfucker all night.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> Someone called and was like, "Hey, this is what you're going to do
Speaker 0: tonight.".
Speaker 0: I'm like,
Speaker 0: "What?".
Speaker 0: >> This is going to be one that I--.
Speaker 0: >> That was fucking--.
Speaker 0: I've got to tell you guys, that was awesome over there.
Speaker 0: Everybody took a fucking flight.
Speaker 0: >> Where are you going?
Speaker 0: >> I was yelling at this guy, "This is nothing for
Speaker 0: me!".
Speaker 0: >> I can't believe that idiot.
Speaker 0: we got upstairs actually got on the ground.
Speaker 0: >> I know.
Speaker 0: I couldn't believe it.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> Everything's filled up, I guess.
Speaker 0: >> How many cells are in--.
Speaker 0: >> This is the booking officer.
Speaker 0: Izzy!
Speaker 0: How many cells are at District
Speaker 0: 4? >> 20. >>
Speaker 0: Holy shit, we fucking have one.
Speaker 0: >> We've got one cell.
Speaker 0: >> I need new gloves now.
Speaker 0: This thing's a toy the fuck up.
Speaker 0: >> Three females, two juveniles, and five I-15s.
Speaker 0: >> I'd say it turned out to be a little more fun than I expected.
Speaker 0: >> We should just fucking stay in here and pick them off as they come in.
Speaker 0: >> Hope that's not fucking Metrolet coming in with dogs.
Speaker 0: Hey, now.
Speaker 0: Hey, could you do me a favor?
Speaker 0: We had five guys brought to D4 under arrest for being E up at SACS.
Speaker 0: Could you just check on their booking status for me real quick?
Speaker 0: >> They're getting booked right now.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, they are?
Speaker 0: How many guys are we in?
Speaker 0: Do we know?
Speaker 0: Okay, so you already have four booked?
Speaker 0: Okay, awesome.
Speaker 0: So I'm going to send Astrid in to start that report, and I'm going to be relieving Almeida momentarily once we get these next four transported.
Speaker 0: All right, thanks.
Speaker 0: They're all being E at SACS.
Speaker 0: Yeah, this is like fucking our fishing ground.
Speaker 0: >> Hey, I'm done, man.
Speaker 0: You have to have these rusty-ass fucking cups, man.
Speaker 0: >> So they're getting transported to 18.
Speaker 0: You guys are both going to get out of here.
Speaker 0: >> You're going to write this?
Speaker 0: >> No, the first five are going to be booked to four, so he's going to write that one, and then I'm thinking the other four might not be for a while, so they're not going to wait for the one-one on them anyway, right?
Speaker 0: >> Yeah.
Speaker 0: >> I find it hard to believe that you guys don't have WD-40 in the fucking thing.
Speaker 0: >> These things have just been sitting in the microwave for a while.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> What the fucking Walgreens here?
Speaker 0: >> They're hitting the Walgreens again.
Speaker 0: >> Prescription?
Speaker 0: >> Where?
Speaker 0: >> This is safe back there.
Speaker 0: >> I think so, yeah.
Speaker 0: the prescription.
Speaker 0: >> We got to go back to the van.
Speaker 0: Is your bag in there?
Speaker 0: >> My bag's in the van.
Speaker 0: >> If it's still there.
Speaker 0: >> They might have told it, yeah.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> If they wanted it, they can have it.
Speaker 0: >> Oh, in that bag of watches?
Speaker 0: >> Look at the bag.
Speaker 0: >> Jesus.
Speaker 0: >> He didn't come in here without a plan.
Speaker 0: I know this is an expedition.
Speaker 0: >> Yeah?
Speaker 0: >> Actually, we need security to come back here.
Speaker 0: >> Why didn't they fucking secure it?
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> There's a million fucking phones.
Speaker 0: >> No, I took that one out.
Speaker 0: With the keys.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: >> Fuck 'em.
Speaker 0: >> You guys aren't coming in here with dogs, are you?
Speaker 0: >> Where'd they go?
Speaker 0: >> We heard 'em barking.
Speaker 0: >> You didn't see a group down here?
Speaker 0: >> We heard the dogs, but we didn't see any of them.
Speaker 0: [beep] >> We got this place, huh?
Speaker 0: >> We've made fucking 11 arrests here so far.
Speaker 0: [radio chatter].
Speaker 0: Fuck, it's no shit.
Speaker 0: It's pretty good, but even if we can get to your crew, it's... Okay, 'cause I'd like, you know, to assist Brookline and have someone get the info from Brookline for their B&E, and we'll handle that for them, just get all the info of what they observed.
Speaker 0: Alright, shit.
Speaker 0: Did you copy that, Brian?
Speaker 0: I am sorry.
Speaker 0: Tampa, we're not off of Brookline, this is a completely separate incident.
Speaker 0: Inside Saks, what's happening?
Speaker 0: Delta, Charlie 1.
Speaker 0: Charlie 1.
Speaker 0: Metro.
Speaker 0: Oh, Metro.
Speaker 0: Do we have someone that can assist Brookline up there?
Speaker 0: Trying to find someone.
Speaker 0: Yeah, it's Metro, Metro.
Speaker 0: That's the same guy that was just here.
Speaker 0: I didn't even see him come in.
Speaker 0: No, he like, came from another way, I think.
Speaker 0: Did he come from under there?
Speaker 0: No, there's one over there, too.
Speaker 0: Delta 9-3 to 4-2-5, it's on scene.
Speaker 0: We're getting a couple.
Speaker 0: Hey, let's grab two, guys.
Speaker 0: I don't know why I said that.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: You're not going to puke on me, are you?
Speaker 0: No, I'm fine.
Speaker 0: Got to go to the right.
Speaker 0: You're going to have to slide under this here.
Speaker 0: Watch your head, okay?
Speaker 0: And watch the glass.
Speaker 0: You're not going to run.
Speaker 0: Watch out for traffic.
Speaker 0: The same way you came in.
Speaker 0: Alright.
Speaker 0: Is there any chance we can get a bike dog to take this kid out?
Speaker 0: Be in the building.
Speaker 0: Is there any chance we can get a bus down to patch his leg up?
Speaker 0: Yeah, give me a second.
Speaker 0: There's supposed to be a transport on the way.
Speaker 0: Okay, for you guys, right?
Speaker 0: You just need an ambulance?
Speaker 0: Yeah, just so they can clean it up.
Speaker 0: Radio 9-7-0-6.
Speaker 0: Steve, could you start H&H to the Ring Road side of Saks?
Speaker 0: Nemlick, their canine, took a guy out.
Speaker 0: He's got an injury to the leg.
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 0: All set.
Speaker 0: Is he going to puke again?
Speaker 0: I think so.
Speaker 0: Try it.
Speaker 0: Get out of here, clown.
Speaker 0: Stupid shipment.
Speaker 0: It's not like the old days.
Speaker 0: If this had been the '80s, there would have been a lot of cracked skulls.
Speaker 0: It would have been a wrap.
Speaker 0: You'd have to see him being in the hospital.
Speaker 0: You can't loosen them once they get tightened.
Speaker 0: Okay, I have the number.
Speaker 0: Is that the Western Hotel, is it?
Speaker 0: Yeah, that area.
Speaker 0: Okay, on the way.
Speaker 0: Radio 9-7-0-6.
Speaker 0: 9-7-0-6, sir.
Speaker 0: Sir, can I get a status of the transport that was requested by the 9-0-3 at Saks?
Speaker 0: I'm looking at that right now, stand by.
Speaker 0: 2-2.
Speaker 0: Where are we bringing state police arrests?
Speaker 0: Call of duty, right?
Speaker 0: Being told 18 at this time.
Speaker 0: What the fuck?
Speaker 0: We're getting cars now.
Speaker 0: Any more?
Speaker 0: Radio 9-7-0-6, you got Ambulance 24 and a tactical unit on the way to Austin.
Speaker 0: Yeah, T-3 just pulled up.
Speaker 0: Still need the transport for these four prisoners.
Speaker 0: Okay, and the wagon, the Harry wagon is coming.
Speaker 0: They're working off a list and they should be alive.
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 0: Okay, he's on ring road now.
Speaker 0: I've been asking.
Speaker 0: Dude, who is this freaking?
Speaker 0: 4-2-5?
Speaker 0: who's answering up?
Speaker 0: He said the Harry wagon's coming.
Speaker 0: Well, that's even better because now we can get them all over there.
Speaker 0: They're up there.
Speaker 0: The Nemlech guy, the dog bit this guy, I guess, on the leg.
Speaker 0: No, no, up the back there.
Speaker 0: Oh, he's up there.
Speaker 0: How's it all, 81?
Speaker 0: Stand by to take the car to security.
Speaker 0: 20-0, Adler.
Speaker 0: I'm at the one at 285 Columbus, right at Columbus and Clarendon.
Speaker 0: Columbus and Clarendon, car to stand by until we get that secured.
Speaker 0: Got away from us, but he still got caught.
Speaker 0: You guys going to transport them?
Speaker 0: Where'd they go?
Speaker 0: Oh, they're over there.
Speaker 0: Probably like Tufts or something.
Speaker 0: You guys going to transport?
Speaker 0: Where at?
Speaker 0: Tufts?
Speaker 0: Alright.
Speaker 0: He said they're going to... Sorry, what?
Speaker 0: Okay.
Speaker 0: They're going to Tufts.
Speaker 0: Tufts.
Speaker 0: Tufts?
Speaker 0: Okay, I'll send... We grab all your info.
Speaker 0: Alright, do you know where the state police prisoners are?
Speaker 0: Are those males?
Speaker 0: Yes, one.
Speaker 0: One male.
Speaker 0: Okay, stand by.
Speaker 0: They're saying to bring them over to Dave Boulevard.
Speaker 0: He's still got cuffs on, Brian.
Speaker 0: Yeah, we're going to have to summons him.
Speaker 0: Get him transported.
Speaker 0: You want me to take him off?
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Hey, we're not going to guide him, so he's not in custody.
Speaker 0: I'll grab the cuffs off.
Speaker 0: I was going to say, he's wearing somebody's cuffs.
Speaker 0: You're going to get summonsed to court, okay?
Speaker 0: Because we don't have enough people to watch you at the hospital.
Speaker 0: Can you lean forward?
Speaker 0: I'm going to take the cuffs off you.
Speaker 0: A little more, if you can.
Speaker 0: Let me see if they've got enough room down in the barracks for all five of them.
Speaker 0: Sorry if I'm pinching you.
Speaker 0: There it goes.
Speaker 0: Correct me if I'm wrong, boss, there's a size one.
Speaker 0: We're good.
Speaker 0: You got him off, yeah?
Speaker 0: Yeah, we got him off.
Speaker 0: Alright.
Speaker 0: You want to take me too?
Speaker 0: Why?
Speaker 0: I'm suicidal.
Speaker 0: Don't say that.
Speaker 0: Hey, is he just going to be a summoner?
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: We can't guide him.
Speaker 0: Yeah, no problem.
Speaker 0: I'm good with that.
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 0: Ask him.
Speaker 0: if he can take one more dog bite, then he's free to go.
Speaker 0: Ha!
Speaker 0: I think you can just go left on Boylston, the wrong way.
Speaker 0: Alright, they have one CC punched for four so far.
Speaker 0: Do you need another one?
Speaker 0: Okay, 202.
Speaker 0: Thanks, man.
Speaker 0: See you later.
Speaker 0: Okay.
Speaker 0: You got him?
Speaker 0: You need a number?
Speaker 0: Yeah, why don't you have Almeda?
Speaker 0: grab all his info and... Yeah, and we'll just have him right here.
Speaker 0: Alright, we got him now.
Speaker 0: He's behind the plate now, so... He's behind it now.
Speaker 0: Then what?
Speaker 0: Nope, he's on it.
Speaker 0: That's it.
Speaker 0: He's down.
Speaker 0: Yellow 424 is 202.
Speaker 0: Yes.
Speaker 0: And when you can, 5449 to provide the info.
Speaker 0: Oh, my God.
Speaker 0: So, Cap, I'm going to get rid of... Delta 982.
Speaker 0: Anybody have a key to the subplot?
Speaker 0: Alright.
Speaker 0: Yeah, yeah.
Speaker 0: Operator at 7541, come on in here.
Speaker 0: Anybody with a key to that vehicle?
Speaker 0: Are you guys good right here?
Speaker 0: Hey, as long as that guy is all set... You got all the info for that guy that just went?
Speaker 0: I didn't get any info.
Speaker 0: I got his name and social.
Speaker 0: Okay.
Speaker 0: Who's writing it?
Speaker 0: Is he?
Speaker 0: This is who I'm about to talk to.
Speaker 0: We're going to add... The guys that we just transported to AT, you're doing that in the morning, right?
Speaker 0: Yep.
Speaker 0: You need to add in his info.
Speaker 0: That guy that is now going to be summoned is also B and E sacks.
Speaker 0: Which guy?
Speaker 0: The one that the dog bit.
Speaker 0: The guy that just got bit?
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Another two lines.
Speaker 0: Another two lines, yeah.
Speaker 0: Also a suspect fucking stopped by a canine and officer.
Speaker 0: With four canines around him.
Speaker 0: Fucking moron.
Speaker 0: He was still running.
Speaker 0: We walked up like 11 people in there.
Speaker 0: I know.
Speaker 0: Well, we held it.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: We were chasing them around there.
Speaker 0: It was wild.
Speaker 0: I get five arrests for the state.
Speaker 0: They're all state prisoners.
Speaker 0: Three go to State Boulevard and two go to Massport Hall Road.
Speaker 0: I didn't have to do a thing besides cuff them.
Speaker 0: Okay.
Speaker 0: I think it's only one of them going to be going to the state.
Speaker 0: I guess Boston's going to take the fall off.
Speaker 0: I had two sets of cuffs.
Speaker 0: Trooper gave me another one.
Speaker 0: I ran out of everything.
Speaker 0: Do you need them now?
Speaker 0: No.
Speaker 0: Fuck.
Speaker 0: Done.
Speaker 0: I'm a chief, so I typically don't cuff people.
Speaker 0: If you need them.
Speaker 0: No, I'll be fine.
Speaker 0: I think he's going to cut us loose anyway.
Speaker 0: Oh, maybe.
Speaker 0: If you're sure you don't need them.
Speaker 0: God knows what we're going to run into.
Speaker 0: Thanks, chief.
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 0: P.J.
Speaker 0: Kearney, go up.
Speaker 0: Go up.
Speaker 0: Kilo 104 on the assignment.
Speaker 0: Me.
Speaker 0: Yeah, yeah, no, that's good.
Speaker 0: I got four.
Speaker 0: I'm on the corner and this kid comes flying out the door.
Speaker 0: That's unbelievable.
Speaker 0: There's fucking, Newberry Street, there's eight of us.
Speaker 0: Eight of us.
Speaker 0: And they're fucking, they're breaking into every fucking building.
Speaker 0: They've burned, they've smashed his car right in front of us.
Speaker 0: Drive here.
Speaker 0: Just give me a minute.
Speaker 0: What did you guys say?
Speaker 0: He's tried running around.
Speaker 0: Doesn't, even if, let's say we hit him.
Speaker 0: So if I can walk, at least he's right here.
Speaker 0: He could jump in.
Speaker 0: That's him.
Speaker 0: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Speaker 0: His, uh, his cousin that came up was afraid of him.
Speaker 0: So, you're good to help him.
Speaker 0: Yeah, how?
Speaker 0: Yeah, we'll find him.
Speaker 0: We gotta go find, see if our, our bags are in the van.
Speaker 0: They looted it, though.
Speaker 0: I don't even know what's in it.
Speaker 0: I don't think it was that bad.
Speaker 0: You know, I'm never gonna get a replacement from this goddamn joke of a department.
Speaker 0: Sarge, I'm sorry, what was your name again?
Speaker 0: McRael.
Speaker 0: M-C-G-R-A-E-L.
Speaker 0: So if you're clear, I'll take both bags.
Speaker 0: I'll make sure.
Speaker 0: Delta 903?
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Are we going right now?
Speaker 0: Yeah, we'll get you guys out of here.
Speaker 0: Yes.
Speaker 0: Sarge, is he gonna be securing for the night?
Speaker 0: Oh, yeah, let's go.
Speaker 0: Yeah, I got a Gray and a Russell report.
Speaker 0: Sure.
Speaker 0: For five of these turns.
Speaker 0: Thank you, guys.
Speaker 0: All right.
Speaker 0: Ha!
Speaker 0: Yeah, right?
Speaker 0: Well, it was a pleasure, gentlemen.
Speaker 0: Good job, boys, let's do this again, huh?
Speaker 0: Fuckin' won't be a night to forget.
Speaker 0: We'll do it.
Speaker 0: Well done.
Speaker 0: Good job.
Speaker 0: Thanks, guys.
Speaker 0: Yeah, two's there.
Speaker 0: Two's there.
Speaker 0: I think the seven's another one.
Speaker 0: Oh, yeah.
Speaker 0: When they see the media covering this, yeah.
Speaker 0: And the media will paint it as a peaceful protest.
Speaker 0: Completely overreacting.
Speaker 0: Without a doubt, they'll do it.
Speaker 0: Should I leave this thing on until we fuckin' get out of here?
Speaker 0: 'Cause you never know what's gonna happen.