Speaker 0: Mike, you've got to lock this thing up, too.
Speaker 0: Spray.
Speaker 0: You got your helmet?
Speaker 0: Mike, let's go.
Speaker 0: They're outside.
Speaker 0: The sergeant was trying to form a line going that way.
Speaker 0: Going across.
Speaker 0: Watch that way.
Speaker 0: You're going to have to wait a few minutes, buddy.
Speaker 0: Oh, I did.
Speaker 0: He's getting laid in.
Speaker 0: Who?
Speaker 0: Can we go spray the car?
Speaker 0: No, you've got to cut through them.
Speaker 0: Give them a couple of minutes.
Speaker 0: Cross the street and go that way, all right?
Speaker 0: Thank you, guys.
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 0: Be careful.
Speaker 0: What's up?
Speaker 0: When everything's going down down there, I need my girl to know which way she went.
Speaker 0: Yeah, you've got to go that way, ladies.
Speaker 0: She needs to get out of the mercy line.
Speaker 0: No one knows where she is right now.
Speaker 0: Fucking assholes.
Speaker 0: All of you.
Speaker 0: I fucking hate y'all.
Speaker 0: I've been here.
Speaker 0: Keep going that way.
Speaker 0: Keep going that way, ma'am.
Speaker 0: You don't deserve to be here.
Speaker 0: Keep going that way.
Speaker 0: Ma'am, keep going that way.
Speaker 0: You don't deserve any of those badges.
Speaker 0: Stop it.
Speaker 0: You don't deserve that badge.
Speaker 0: All right, all right.
Speaker 0: You don't deserve your badge.
Speaker 0: Ma'am, keep going.
Speaker 0: And you don't deserve your badge.
Speaker 0: Fuck you.
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 0: No.
Speaker 0: Listen to us.
Speaker 0: I don't need it.
Speaker 0: I can't hear you, ma'am.
Speaker 0: I think that's going to be shut down.
Speaker 0: You might have to go to Haymarket or State Street.
Speaker 0: South Station?
Speaker 0: We are going to Ashmont.
Speaker 0: So you've got to take the red line.
Speaker 0: But, ma'am, I'm asking you.
Speaker 0: If they say we have to get on that car.
Speaker 0: We go South Station.
Speaker 0: You want to go South Station?
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Why don't you head down this way, ma'am.
Speaker 0: Where's your friend?
Speaker 0: My nephew.
Speaker 0: Come on.
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 0: Yeah, be careful.
Speaker 0: Be careful going through there.
Speaker 0: Excuse me.
Speaker 0: What's up, buddy?
Speaker 0: Sorry if I can get through here.
Speaker 0: My apartment's closed.
Speaker 0: They've got to shut down for now.
Speaker 0: Give them a couple of minutes.
Speaker 0: We're hoping to open this up.
Speaker 0: It's a whole district to start with.
Speaker 0: No one's going through.
Speaker 0: You're here.
Speaker 0: You can take anybody who comes through.
Speaker 0: That's on me.
Speaker 0: I thought she was by herself.
Speaker 0: Just go straight that way?
Speaker 0: Go that way because everybody's walking this way.
Speaker 0: Yes, sir.
Speaker 0: Got you.
Speaker 0: Next right is my right.
Speaker 0: You can't stay in the heat.
Speaker 0: You shouldn't want to come down here.
Speaker 0: Education, welfare, too.
Speaker 0: Y'all press us for education.
Speaker 0: Not me, but you.
Speaker 0: I know you're not a white man.
Speaker 0: I can't really tell you.
Speaker 0: You look Hispanic.
Speaker 0: You can't even tell me.
Speaker 0: Y'all feel any sympathy for this?
Speaker 0: I mean to leave me out there bad.
Speaker 0: This is one of them things about an hour right now.
Speaker 0: Biggest question I always have for you guys.
Speaker 0: Why the fuck does it take about four or five properties?
Speaker 0: I swear to God.
Speaker 0: People up on the scaffolding.
Speaker 0: And it really will only take these big ass houses.
Speaker 0: They will only take them.
Speaker 0: Y'all really, y'all.
Speaker 0: It is what it is.
Speaker 0: Just in general with all this shit.
Speaker 0: Not tonight.
Speaker 0: I mean, yeah.
Speaker 0: It's nice when I fucking win stuff.
Speaker 0: I wish I had a jacket.
Speaker 0: What's that?
Speaker 0: That's why I walk around.
Speaker 0: It's not too much.
Speaker 0: It's not personally y'all.
Speaker 0: But y'all love the uniform.
Speaker 0: That's why I run.
Speaker 0: We could go around.
Speaker 0: I don't know.
Speaker 0: We're trying to find a street.
Speaker 0: I don't know where A. Walk that way, ladies.
Speaker 0: If you want to go around, we got to walk that way.
Speaker 0: There's A. Winter Street.
Speaker 0: What is it there?
Speaker 0: A. Winter Street.
Speaker 0: That's where she is.
Speaker 0: Yeah, she's going to have to come up here.
Speaker 0: I don't know where that is.
Speaker 0: You won't be able to go down.
Speaker 0: You might have to walk around.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: You know what I'm saying?
Speaker 0: Same uniform.
Speaker 0: Same name.
Speaker 0: Same shirt.
Speaker 0: But like I said, I'm not blaming y'all.
Speaker 0: I'm just asking y'all to get somewhere.
Speaker 0: I ain't here to start no shit.
Speaker 0: Let me ask you a question.
Speaker 0: Like I told you, I used to run when I was in the military.
Speaker 0: I used to run.
Speaker 0: Fear is good.
Speaker 0: Fear is healthy.
Speaker 0: It's an emotion.
Speaker 0: And that fucking guy, he didn't care.
Speaker 0: He didn't care.
Speaker 0: How many people are there going to come up to you?
Speaker 0: From here?
Speaker 0: I have no idea.
Speaker 0: I don't know where they are.
Speaker 0: I don't want to sleep in anybody's eyes.
Speaker 0: I don't know why I can't sleep.
Speaker 0: It's an emotion.
Speaker 0: Fear is good.
Speaker 0: It's good.
Speaker 0: emotional empathize, because that guy in the White House, he couldn't empathize with people's shit, you know?
Speaker 0: The industry is good.
Speaker 0: Tan pants, black shirt, black hat, what a bother.
Speaker 0: You playing jokes right now?
Speaker 0: You think this whole ride is a joke?
Speaker 0: You gonna make jokes right now?
Speaker 0: Fuck do I care?
Speaker 0: Fuck off!
Speaker 0: Ain't no jokin', man.
Speaker 0: Why the fuck you gon' play around that, man?
Speaker 0: No, you don't play around that, bro.
Speaker 0: You don't play around no shit like that.
Speaker 0: You know I'm hurtin' these times, so oh, fuck Tom Brady, number two.
Speaker 0: Fuck you, man.
Speaker 0: Fuck you personally.
Speaker 0: Kill us.
Speaker 0: Go ahead anymore.
Speaker 0: What are you gonna do?
Speaker 0: Kill us?
Speaker 0: That's what you're gonna do?
Speaker 0: That's all you know how to do?
Speaker 0: Cause you didn't go to school, right?
Speaker 0: Kill the people, kill the people, kill the people, murderers, murderers, murderers, murderers, murderers, all murderers, all of y'all, murderers, you don't stand up for your people, huh, you're not even white, you're standing with them, you're not even white, why are you standing with them, can you take a knee, can you take a knee, can you take a knee, can you guys take a knee, I don't think so, we have two virus now, coronavirus and police virus, that's two virus, fuck you guys, take your way that way, take your way that way, we're going this way, you take your way that way, you're the boss.
Speaker 0: right, we want to go this way, this is a public street, this is our street, we frequent this street, not you, not him, not him, we do, we do, you never was here, we do, you got to kill people, you stand up for them.
Speaker 0: right, you're black, you stand up for them, you're a shame, you just take the money and suck it up your ass, I'm scared of you, shame on you, shame on you, I feel bad, take a knee, can you take a knee, can you take a knee, can you, stop killing us, stop killing us, take a knee, is that what you're taught, look away, look above me, shit, I don't know, look at me, jokester man, they switch, they switch, they switch posts, are you the boss here, are you the boss, I can tell, I can tell, I can just tell, not just because of the stuff, as it puts you across, I didn't notice that until after I asked the question, but I can just tell, I got faith in God, I swear to God, I love my city, that's why, if you see your partner do something dirty, would you speak up, sure, would you speak up?
Speaker 0: if you see your partner do something dirty, because this is our street, what are you doing in our streets, my man, my man, no, I can tell because he's not looking me in my eyes, no, they don't give a fuck, he's not looking me in my eyes, look at me, look at me, you're a dog, I feel bad for you, you shouldn't read a book, have you ever read a book, let me ask him a question, it doesn't look like it, I'm not scared of you, let me ask him a question, let me ask him a question, let me ask him a question, do you hear my neck, this is how I'm not afraid, let me ask him a question, did you take an oath to uphold the constitution, no, he doesn't know what that means, he knows what it means, he doesn't read a book, I took the oath, so if you see your partner do something dirty, would you speak up, you're standing up for your people, you make it hard for the people, you put that on everybody, I don't make it hard for the people to get to their cars, are you doing the right thing, that's why he's looking at you in my eyes, hey my brother, that shit's blocked, what's that, murderers, murderers, murderers, murderers all over the streets, don't be nice, you know what I'm talking about, you're the same, you was in our parents' school for nine months, all the same, like what do you mean, like yeah, the big man's skin, they treat us different, you was in our, you could tell by who looked you in the eye, that's what I'm saying, that's what I'm saying, god damn, I know everybody's father told them when a man's talking to him, look him in the eye, that's what y'all dads taught me, that's what my dad told me, that's what my dad taught me, he looked at me in my eyes, I respect that, you have to understand, I know, oh yeah, that's true, that's true, people are throwing things at you, okay, we're throwing things but you was killing us, do you care about that, do you care about somebody getting killed, I do, no you don't, because throwing shit at you ain't the same thing as kneeling you down, do you know that, and I bet you would kneel somebody down if it was black, right, because you white, that's what you guys do, so don't come here talking shit because we know what you do, and stop taking over people's streets, it's not okay, we're tired of you, can't you see that, yeah, of you, of him, of everyone else, police virus, coronavirus, we're tired of your virus, yes I am, yes I am, proud to be one, yeah, that's why she's going ahead right now, proud to be one, yeah, that's a CV statement, Cabral shit, and I'm one of them, do you know him, I'm one of them exactly, because you don't stand for peace, you don't read, you don't know history, all you know is white money, that's all you know, Cabral standing up for our people, for you, for your ass to be here talking shit, and you're not even standing up for them, you're just taking advantage of their ass, you're just giving them money, you're so fucking insane, I'm telling you, I'm telling you, they started checking out the people, now you guys are going to start shooting, you're waiting for it, it's just starting to turn up right now, I'm not scared of you, I'm not scared of your camera, get right here, and then if I start running, excuse me, how can we get to the train station, we don't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we can't, we Okay, well I don't give a shit about the money.
Speaker 0: I mean clearly they do, what else will they do?
Speaker 0: Yeah, that's why they're here.
Speaker 0: The money, right?
Speaker 0: You don't know what else to do.
Speaker 0: Exactly.
Speaker 0: They can't be an engineer, they can't be a doctor, tiny scientists.
Speaker 0: All they got to do is use violence.
Speaker 0: Teachers don't make money?
Speaker 0: Right.
Speaker 0: Teachers are smart as shit.
Speaker 0: I feel bad for teachers.
Speaker 0: Teaching us how to fight people.
Speaker 0: I ain't telling you.
Speaker 0: I'm not scared of you.
Speaker 0: Why are you looking at me like that?
Speaker 0: I'm not scared of black people, even white people.
Speaker 0: I'm not scared of you.
Speaker 0: He wants to hurt you, don't let him hurt you.
Speaker 0: He's not going to hurt me.
Speaker 0: He's not going to hurt me because I didn't do anything to him.
Speaker 0: So he's not going to hurt me.
Speaker 0: They don't need that anymore.
Speaker 0: They know that the brotherhood will be behind them.
Speaker 0: I don't give a shit.
Speaker 0: We're going to keep protesting.
Speaker 0: They killed many of them.
Speaker 0: I'm not the only one.
Speaker 0: Go ahead and murder people.
Speaker 0: What's great about you guys is that it's a landmark.
Speaker 0: I'm trying to find people and they know where I am.
Speaker 0: It's funny.
Speaker 0: So your bright yellow jackets are effective.
Speaker 0: You're going to kill me too?
Speaker 0: You're going to kill me?
Speaker 0: You're going to hit me?
Speaker 0: Kill us.
Speaker 0: Do you think Michael Vick?
Speaker 0: I feel like he repented.
Speaker 0: I feel like the second half of his career is totally valid.
Speaker 0: You can't go this way.
Speaker 0: I already got yelled at.
Speaker 0: Is the army going to get sued?
Speaker 0: You can't.
Speaker 0: But people from Boston don't like the Eagles, right?
Speaker 0: I'm telling you, you can't.
Speaker 0: Do the Patriots have rivals?
Speaker 0: No one knows if they're any good.
Speaker 0: The Jets suck.
Speaker 0: Who's the Patriots' rival?
Speaker 0: I don't know.
Speaker 0: Do you like football?
Speaker 0: Do you follow any sports?
Speaker 0: What do you follow?
Speaker 0: Basketball.
Speaker 0: Not a good time.
Speaker 0: Not a good time to talk about sports.
Speaker 0: I mean, listen.
Speaker 0: Best case scenario, that's all that happens.
Speaker 0: All you do is talk tonight.
Speaker 0: No one gets hurt.
Speaker 0: People just stand and chant.
Speaker 0: We're allowed to do that.
Speaker 0: We should be happy that we're talking.
Speaker 0: It's like a positive thing.
Speaker 0: So much more positive.
Speaker 0: This is also still your job.
Speaker 0: How many more people are going to come?
Speaker 0: If I'm having trouble, you're holding me up.
Speaker 0: What if I'm having trouble?
Speaker 0: Bombing?
Speaker 0: Oh.
Speaker 0: One of them are having trouble.
Speaker 0: All right.
Speaker 0: This is our money.
Speaker 0: we're going to spend on protests, huh?
Speaker 0: Who wants to stop killing people?
Speaker 0: That would work.
Speaker 0: They didn't kill the people.
Speaker 0: Yes, they did.
Speaker 0: Because they all supported you.
Speaker 0: That's the thing.
Speaker 0: They support the system.
Speaker 0: They are the system.
Speaker 0: They're by the system.
Speaker 0: They could have been protesting, but they're here standing up for the system.
Speaker 0: It is their problem.
Speaker 0: Yes.
Speaker 0: They're not.
Speaker 0: We don't have... We're tired of not being fair, so now we're fighting for justice.
Speaker 0: I got shoes on.
Speaker 0: Adidas.
Speaker 0: I don't mean to be like that.
Speaker 0: Absolutely.
Speaker 0: I'm not shutting you up at all.
Speaker 0: Like I said, you know, I don't want them to have that negative indication about us.
Speaker 0: We're all here for peace, but we've got to improve it.
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 0: Are all the streets closed?
Speaker 0: One this way?
Speaker 0: I have to walk to South Station.
Speaker 0: So go all the way down here, as far as you can, take a left onto Essex.
Speaker 0: Down here.
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 0: Essex is crazy.
Speaker 0: Essex and Wash.
Speaker 0: He got it.
Speaker 0: He got maced.
Speaker 0: He's getting rinsed out with milk.
Speaker 0: They were pouring milk in his eyes.
Speaker 0: Can I get that?
Speaker 0: There's way too many of us here.
Speaker 0: They call for help.
Speaker 0: We've got to go to the other place.
Speaker 0: They've got to pull some of us off.
Speaker 0: I'm sick of that man's cold blood.
Speaker 0: I'm tired of it.
Speaker 0: They don't have free minds.
Speaker 0: They're slaves to the system.
Speaker 0: You guys are a part of the machine.
Speaker 0: The system is built.
Speaker 0: They're killing the systematic.
Speaker 0: The shit is systematic.
Speaker 0: We need a better system.
Speaker 0: They killed him.
Speaker 0: He's fucking dead.
Speaker 0: Look what you fucking did.
Speaker 0: Your eyes don't fucking look like his.
Speaker 0: Your eyes don't look like his.
Speaker 0: Look what you fucking did.
Speaker 0: They killed him in cold blood.
Speaker 0: That could have been me.
Speaker 0: That could have been you.
Speaker 0: Cold blood.
Speaker 0: That's in front of the car.
Speaker 0: Traffic control.
Speaker 0: You're a bitch.
Speaker 0: And you're a bitch.
Speaker 0: We finally got body care.
Speaker 0: It's good.
Speaker 0: We need a better system.
Speaker 0: The power is with the people.
Speaker 0: Not with the police.
Speaker 0: The power is with the people, not with the police.
Speaker 0: Now they told us to bring the gas masks.
Speaker 0: I see the human being inside all of you guys.
Speaker 0: And I know you all saw the video.
Speaker 0: I know you saw the video, sir.
Speaker 0: That shit was cold.
Speaker 0: People are tired of this shit.
Speaker 0: We need fairness.
Speaker 0: They all need to be arrested.
Speaker 0: All of them need to be arrested.
Speaker 0: And they all need to be tried.
Speaker 0: For killing innocent men.
Speaker 0: In custody, handcuffs.
Speaker 0: What kind of shit is that?
Speaker 0: I know y'all can all relate as humans.
Speaker 0: Not with the fucking badge.
Speaker 0: They killed that man.
Speaker 0: Cold blood.
Speaker 0: Shit is systematic.
Speaker 0: We need a better system.
Speaker 0: It's not just George Floyd.
Speaker 0: It's too many.
Speaker 0: Too many in too many states.
Speaker 0: Too many departments.
Speaker 0: What kind of training are they giving out here?
Speaker 0: What kind of shit is this?
Speaker 0: These are the people.
Speaker 0: We need arrests.
Speaker 0: Accountability.
Speaker 0: That's what we need.
Speaker 0: Watch them from behind now.
Speaker 0: She's got the stick now.
Speaker 0: We need a better system.
Speaker 0: We need police.
Speaker 0: Working on relationships with communities.
Speaker 0: That's what we need.
Speaker 0: We don't need robots.
Speaker 0: We need people.
Speaker 0: Connecting with people.
Speaker 0: We don't want machines.
Speaker 0: There's a white supremacist stabbing people a couple blocks down.
Speaker 0: Who do I call about that?
Speaker 0: What do I do?
Speaker 0: What?
Speaker 0: You guys are not in one one.
Speaker 0: How do we get out?
Speaker 0: Stewart's all the way down there.
Speaker 0: I have to go that way.
Speaker 0: How do I get out?
Speaker 0: Is there any way to get out of here?
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 0: You came here without a plan?
Speaker 0: Yep.
Speaker 0: Am I supposed to be?
Speaker 0: What, it shut off?
Speaker 0: Yeah, so... I hope you boxed them all in here and then hit them with the glass.
Speaker 0: Where are you going?
Speaker 0: Home.
Speaker 0: Where is home?
Speaker 0: Like, we need to get to a train station.
Speaker 0: We're going to have to get to... Government Center?
Speaker 0: Go up?
Speaker 0: Go up this way.
Speaker 0: Yep.
Speaker 0: It's going to go down the hill.
Speaker 0: We confirm one.
Speaker 0: Is there somebody else?
Speaker 0: Where are you?
Speaker 0: Where are you at?
Speaker 0: We'll be right away, sir.
Speaker 0: What are you looking at?
Speaker 0: There's a cruiser over there.
Speaker 0: It's stupid having the cruisers here.
Speaker 0: What do you mean?
Speaker 0: I'm at Chelsea.
Speaker 0: They've got crowds surrounding the cruiser there.
Speaker 0: That's where they go.
Speaker 0: What do you mean?
Speaker 0: Get my shirt from him, please!
Speaker 0: You've got to hold tight and watch the cruiser.
Speaker 0: Ah, fuck.
Speaker 0: Where's the gas?
Speaker 0: You want to stay here?
Speaker 0: I'll move down there.
Speaker 0: Come on in again.
Speaker 0: Let's go home.
Speaker 0: Educate our police officers.
Speaker 0: Lawyers spend eight years learning football and history.
Speaker 0: What about you?
Speaker 0: I might need it.
Speaker 0: It's seven, eight people this month.
Speaker 0: Stop it, officer.
Speaker 0: I'm going home right now.
Speaker 0: I want to go down to Charles or Boylston.
Speaker 0: That way.
Speaker 0: You know Charles?
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 0: Quick question.
Speaker 0: Since the trains and buses are closed down, are you guys covering all the streets?
Speaker 0: We don't know.
Speaker 0: We're just staying here.
Speaker 0: So there's really an exit for MSS.
Speaker 0: If I want to go home, I'm going to stay for another few minutes.
Speaker 0: We're going running up there again.
Speaker 0: No.
Speaker 0: No, you can't.
Speaker 0: The cruiser now.
Speaker 0: Go this way.
Speaker 0: We have to go up and around.
Speaker 0: Are you going to eat?
Speaker 0: He's got a glass bottle.
Speaker 0: This one right here.
Speaker 0: Walk in that way.
Speaker 0: It's probably an incendiary.
Speaker 0: You got yours?
Speaker 0: You got your mask?
Speaker 0: It's on?
Speaker 0: Put it on.
Speaker 0: You got your mask?
Speaker 0: What's that?
Speaker 0: No.
Speaker 0: Am I seeing things?
Speaker 0: It's smashed.
Speaker 0: Chill.
Speaker 0: Heads up.
Speaker 0: How are they going to do that?
Speaker 0: How are they going to push people up here?
Speaker 0: Where are they pushing people?
Speaker 0: Where are they pushing people from?
Speaker 0: Up here.
Speaker 0: Heads up.
Speaker 0: Come on.
Speaker 0: How do you like that?
Speaker 0: You're not allowed to use your mask.
Speaker 0: Police!
Speaker 0: I don't know what you're talking about.
Speaker 0: Order him.
Speaker 0: I'm here for no ill intent, I'm here for no ill intent, this is for George Floyd, this is for George Floyd, this is for George Floyd, this is for George Floyd, this is for George Floyd, this is for George Floyd, this is for George Floyd.
Speaker 0: Anybody who doesn't have a mask, you're going to have to pull off the line back.
Speaker 0: Anybody who doesn't have a mask, you're going to have to move them back when they launch.
Speaker 0: There we go, they got the right to shoot people in the back, I don't know if you guys can see that.
Speaker 0: Here we go, coming up behind ya.
Speaker 0: Alright guys, we got to work on it.
Speaker 0: Move!
Speaker 0: Ya asked me nicely, don't act proud of me.
Speaker 0: Don't be proud of me.
Speaker 0: I ain't do shit.
Speaker 0: I got a right.
Speaker 0: Freedom of press.
Speaker 0: I ain't doing nothing at ya.
Speaker 0: My name is sitting right next to me.
Speaker 0: I ain't do shit.
Speaker 0: I don't have a mask, so.
Speaker 0: Hey dad.
Speaker 0: No, no, no, no.
Speaker 0: Sit him down somewhere.
Speaker 0: Yeah, come over here.
Speaker 0: Sit on this.
Speaker 0: Sit down.
Speaker 0: Where'd you get hit?
Speaker 0: In the back.
Speaker 0: You're fucking dead.
Speaker 0: Good.
Speaker 0: For everybody.
Speaker 0: Everybody?
Speaker 0: Everybody.
Speaker 0: Find me with the fucking brick.
Speaker 0: Bring the brick.
Speaker 0: what?
Speaker 0: Brick.
Speaker 0: What's that?
Speaker 0: It's done.
Speaker 0: We gotta get move.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Why isn't?
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 0: Guys, stop bringing this line.
Speaker 0: I want this line here.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 0: Uh huh.
Speaker 0: One time.
Speaker 0: Right.
Speaker 0: Okay.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: What?
Speaker 0: Oh, you have a question?
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Really?
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 0: What's the next one?
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: That's cool, right?
Speaker 0: That's cool.
Speaker 0: I know.
Speaker 0: Yeah, I didn't do this as a police force, but understand our frustration.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Understand our frustration.
Speaker 0: You guys didn't do this.
Speaker 0: I understand our frustration as a whole, especially for the people.
Speaker 0: That's one.
Speaker 0: Yeah, we fucking shit up.
Speaker 0: Understand that.
Speaker 0: Hey, Jamie, we got to gain advantage with the fucking smoke.
Speaker 0: So we got to get around and fucking to the back and fucking that way.
Speaker 0: That's it.
Speaker 0: Oh, yeah.
Speaker 0: All right.
Speaker 0: We're gonna sit here and get shit thrown at us.
Speaker 0: We're gonna fucking do something.
Speaker 0: You want to focus on?
Speaker 0: You gotta move on the fucking Eddie.
Speaker 0: That's what I think.
Speaker 0: But all right, guys.
Speaker 0: Yeah, let's just fucking all over the place.
Speaker 0: I can't tell who the fuck is who right now.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Yeah, they come with flaming shit stuff.
Speaker 0: Guys, right.
Speaker 0: Stay in line, right?
Speaker 0: Stay in a tight line.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 0: All right.
Speaker 0: I'm gonna go.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: No, no, no, no.
Speaker 0: Here we go.
Speaker 0: Coming this way.
Speaker 0: Number one.
Speaker 0: Got it.
Speaker 0: No, no.
Speaker 0: Real close.
Speaker 0: What's the location?
Speaker 0: We're in the car.
Speaker 0: Make sure we have a car.
Speaker 0: Sure.
Speaker 0: There's a point.
Speaker 0: All right.
Speaker 0: Mhm.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: The wagon again.
Speaker 0: Oh yeah.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Mhm.
Speaker 0: It's up.
Speaker 0: It was a boon.
Speaker 0: Slow down.
Speaker 0: Go together.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Together.
Speaker 0: Oh, hold it.
Speaker 0: Oh, yeah.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: You don't like that.
Speaker 0: I ain't got shit.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Walk that shit off.
Speaker 0: Let's go.
Speaker 0: Well, today's yes.
Speaker 0: Thank you guys.
Speaker 0: Oh, today you guys they still I'll talk about it lined up.
Speaker 0: Hey, you see, what?
Speaker 0: You have all the way down now.
Speaker 0: We have the whole park.
Speaker 0: Okay.
Speaker 0: What?
Speaker 0: What do you call?
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 0: Okay.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: That's right.
Speaker 0: Okay.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Wake the fuck up.
Speaker 0: Get the fuck out of the smoke.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: All right.
Speaker 0: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Speaker 0: Head's up.
Speaker 0: Good enough.
Speaker 0: Alright.
Speaker 0: Pull up.
Speaker 0: Whoa, whoa.
Speaker 0: Fall back.
Speaker 0: Are you harassed?
Speaker 0: Get this guy out of here.
Speaker 0: Get this guy out.
Speaker 0: Throw it like a girl.
Speaker 0: Which one of you guys were bullied in high school, eh?
Speaker 0: Let me rephrase.
Speaker 0: Which one of you weren't bullied in high school, eh?
Speaker 0: Which one of you guys were bullied in high school, eh?
Speaker 0: They're all coming down on the right now.
Speaker 0: People coming down on the right.
Speaker 0: We need some bodies to stay with the fire fighters here.
Speaker 0: Are you watching this?
Speaker 0: Are you there?
Speaker 0: Make sure you don't get too close.
Speaker 0: There's no better way to do this?
Speaker 0: Oh, it's awful.
Speaker 0: Huh?
Speaker 0: Pathetic.
Speaker 0: This is all Antifa.
Speaker 0: Do we have enough help off with fire?
Speaker 0: Do we have enough help with them right now?
Speaker 0: That would be advised.
Speaker 0: We're breaking into the Marshalls.
Speaker 0: That's three-seventy-five.
Speaker 0: Walsh, LEC, over.
Speaker 0: Walsh, over.
Speaker 0: They're ruining my lights over there.
Speaker 0: LEC, this is Marshalls.
Speaker 0: Ralph, Ralph, one.
Speaker 0: Ralph, one.
Speaker 0: Alright, sir.
Speaker 0: We have, uh, we have a fire.
Speaker 0: They're working on the fire right now, on Walsh.
Speaker 0: They've extinguished Walgreen's for now and they're inside.
Speaker 0: Uh, right now we're gonna want to take a test, as extreme as possible.
Speaker 0: I'm not gonna get too close.
Speaker 0: Yeah, do it twice in the water.
Speaker 0: Number one, I got a little bit of pepper.
Speaker 0: Pepper spray in here.
Speaker 0: You got stuff in our eyes.
Speaker 0: We're going to just watch.
Speaker 0: Do you copy?
Speaker 0: What?
Speaker 0: I'm not going to shoot that nigger.
Speaker 0: I'm right here.
Speaker 0: I'm right here, bitch.
Speaker 0: Look at me.
Speaker 0: I'm not going to shoot that nigger.
Speaker 0: He's right here.
Speaker 0: Pussy.
Speaker 0: You're a bitch.
Speaker 0: That shit don't hurt.
Speaker 0: That shit hurts you everywhere.
Speaker 0: Fucking right.
Speaker 0: Watch to the right.
Speaker 0: You're not invited over here, fucker.
Speaker 0: Why is it that part of the park is up for you, huh?
Speaker 0: Hey, right side, right side.
Speaker 0: Right side, right side.
Speaker 0: Get off that fucking roadway.
Speaker 0: Pussy.
Speaker 0: Just scaring them.
Speaker 0: Come on.
Speaker 0: Way to go, rain man.
Speaker 0: Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Speaker 0: Fuck.
Speaker 0: Hey, Hawk.
Speaker 0: Watch out, man.
Speaker 0: I can't detain.
Speaker 0: I want free.
Speaker 0: Get away from me.
Speaker 0: Brooke, ask if you can detain.
Speaker 0: Charlie, we need a transport here at the center gate.
Speaker 0: I'm getting stepped on.
Speaker 0: Legacy, we need a transport here at the center gate.
Speaker 0: It's common.
Speaker 0: Huh?
Speaker 0: You good?
Speaker 0: I think I broke my hand.
Speaker 0: You want to go smoke?
Speaker 0: No.
Speaker 0: Hit me with a brick.
Speaker 0: Transit.
Speaker 0: You guys don't have anything else?
Speaker 0: Watch the pop.
Speaker 0: Pop one.
Speaker 0: Squad formation.
Speaker 0: Here.
Speaker 0: we go down here and move across.
Speaker 0: Down this way.
Speaker 0: Hit him up.
Speaker 0: Pop one.
Speaker 0: Bravo one, center gate.
Speaker 0: Go ahead.
Speaker 0: Post it.
Speaker 0: What are they going to do with the guys that are smoking?
Speaker 0: What's that?
Speaker 0: What are they going to do?
Speaker 0: Pop one.
Speaker 0: I saw Walsh with us, but I don't know where Jason is.
Speaker 0: Where who is?
Speaker 0: Walsh was here.
Speaker 0: And Donnie's here.
Speaker 0: I don't know where.
Speaker 0: I haven't seen Mike Ford.
Speaker 0: Pop one.
Speaker 0: Pop two.
Speaker 0: Get a location of pop two.
Speaker 0: We're inside the corner by pox.
Speaker 0: Pop one.
Speaker 0: Pox, we're going around.
Speaker 0: Go around and pop one.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Well, go ahead.
Speaker 0: To the TV and watch this?
Speaker 0: The other one.
Speaker 0: Get back.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: No.
Speaker 0: Come on, Orla.
Speaker 0: and then you flip the hop, and I'll never find you there.
Speaker 0: You guys know we have a lot of smoke right now, right?
Speaker 0: We've got to get back to speed.
Speaker 0: I don't think we've got anybody back.
Speaker 0: We've got about eight miles to go.
Speaker 0: This is a sharp problem.
Speaker 0: Back.
Speaker 0: You know where Donnie is?
Speaker 0: No.
Speaker 0: I had a detail this morning.
Speaker 0: They were putting these stupid things up, and they told them all.
Speaker 0: because of protest you've got to take them all down.
Speaker 0: They're still here.
Speaker 0: Well, he's with us.
Speaker 0: I'm going to start locking people up.
Speaker 0: It's ridiculous.
Speaker 0: We're gonna lock people up.
Speaker 0: Yeah, should have got them all in the common.
Speaker 0: They ran off.
Speaker 0: Want to get a hold of?
Speaker 0: So tonight.
Speaker 0: All right.
Speaker 0: What do you guys got those sticks for?
Speaker 0: You guys got those sticks for?
Speaker 0: You got those sticks for?
Speaker 0: He's yelling at you.
Speaker 0: He probably got kids.
Speaker 0: You got nothing to lose.
Speaker 0: He's at the walk back.
Speaker 0: Thank you.
Speaker 0: What you got?
Speaker 0: Nobody get caught.
Speaker 0: Lost the tree.
Speaker 0: Get the plate.
Speaker 0: Okay, I got more.
Speaker 0: Funny.
Speaker 0: Yes, I like your body.
Speaker 0: I have.
Speaker 0: I don't know.
Speaker 0: That ain't gonna do it.
Speaker 0: I hate the bikes.
Speaker 0: What, they say?
Speaker 0: you smash them on the computer?
Speaker 0: Yeah, a lot of them.
Speaker 0: Every walk down.
Speaker 0: Echo Gold, you at the winter hauling?
Speaker 0: That's summer hauling.
Speaker 0: Hang on, anybody close to the semi-hundred?
Speaker 0: Three-month, cadets plus fire, engines.
Speaker 0: twenty-two to twenty-four.
Speaker 0: Where's De Silva?
Speaker 0: Juan, anybody else?
Speaker 0: Three-sixty, three-nine-oh-one.
Speaker 0: Just us?
Speaker 0: We're gonna go to the other side of the street.
Speaker 0: He wants me and five people on the other side of the street.
Speaker 0: So, we'll go over there now.
Speaker 0: Go over there now?
Speaker 0: I say we go on the right side.
Speaker 0: Yeah, we'll go up here.
Speaker 0: They're gonna start to all fade to the left.
Speaker 0: Yup.
Speaker 0: Watch these fuckers.
Speaker 0: This kid here is one of the head kids, right here with the red phone.
Speaker 0: Get out of here, you're not coming this way.
Speaker 0: Get out of here.
Speaker 0: You ain't coming this way.
Speaker 0: Street's shut down.
Speaker 0: Walk around.
Speaker 0: Shut down.
Speaker 0: Get there quicker if you walk around.
Speaker 0: Yup, you gotta walk around.
Speaker 0: Thank you, my man.
Speaker 0: Don't let them walk up behind us.
Speaker 0: Where you going?
Speaker 0: Huh?
Speaker 0: I don't know what they're doing.
Speaker 0: All they're doing is driving them to another place that they're gonna break into.
Speaker 0: Are you guys still walking?
Speaker 0: I'll be out here all night, pal.
Speaker 0: What's that?
Speaker 0: I don't know how we got all the way over on this side.
Speaker 0: I don't either.
Speaker 0: There's no sense, because all they're doing is pushing them other places.
Speaker 0: We gotta stop them.
Speaker 0: You know, they're letting them filter out to all the other streets, which they're just gonna damage someplace else.
Speaker 0: Well, they didn't do anything to that block, so let's push them up there, let them trash that place.
Speaker 0: I know.
Speaker 0: This is like all Antifa kids.
Speaker 0: Huh?
Speaker 0: All these kids are like pretty much Antifa now.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Yeah, I think all that's left is all Antifa.
Speaker 0: Mike was saying, anybody passed on what street?
Speaker 0: So he's gotta be at the car now.
Speaker 0: Yeah, I just texted him, because I saw that he calls, and I told him where we were.
Speaker 0: I'd like it if he could get, if he could get, if he could get somebody.
Speaker 0: Lost.
Speaker 0: Yeah, so you pushed them up there.
Speaker 0: What do you think they were gonna do?
Speaker 0: Sarge.
Speaker 0: Will you text Jason and let him know we're here?
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: I can't do this.
Speaker 0: Yeah, I know.
Speaker 0: I got it.
Speaker 0: Good job, boys.
Speaker 0: I'm sorry.
Speaker 0: Fuck.
Speaker 0: I fucked up my hand.
Speaker 0: You all right?
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: I got some big metal from the fire.
Speaker 0: Things in front of the building?
Speaker 0: Right off my chest, man.
Speaker 0: I don't know if I broke my knuckle.
Speaker 0: Did you move it?
Speaker 0: Huh?
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: But now it's getting, it's getting sore now.
Speaker 0: This happened when we were on Winter Street.
Speaker 0: It's chasing them, like.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: And these people are the same people just driving around looking for.
Speaker 0: They just look at it cause damage.
Speaker 0: Is this the same group?
Speaker 0: No, different, different.
Speaker 0: I'm sorry.
Speaker 0: Good job parking there.
Speaker 0: They were all over your car, dude.
Speaker 0: They were climbing all over your car.
Speaker 0: Welcome to Boston.
Speaker 0: Come again.
Speaker 0: How are you?
Speaker 0: Huh?
Speaker 0: At least this is quiet.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Are your ears ringing?
Speaker 0: Oh my God.
Speaker 0: My talk, I can hear my, there's like a beeping.
Speaker 0: My radio.
Speaker 0: Oh my God.
Speaker 0: This is it.
Speaker 0: They just split up.
Speaker 0: Some fucking cops are spraying the shit out of the cops.
Speaker 0: Did you see that?
Speaker 0: No.
Speaker 0: Are they back there now?
Speaker 0: All they did was splinter off so we don't have enough people.
Speaker 0: And then they just keep doing what they want.
Speaker 0: Nobody should be coming up these streets.
Speaker 0: These people don't live on this street.
Speaker 0: They're here to do one thing, cause mayhem.
Speaker 0: It's the Antifa people and they suck all these other people into doing the same thing.
Speaker 0: Look at them throwing shit around over there.
Speaker 0: Four young girls trashing the plants in front of Webster Bank.
Speaker 0: And we sit and watch.
Speaker 0: The superintendent told us to stay here?
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: I don't know what's going on.
Speaker 0: Do you want to head up to Floyd Taylor's?
Speaker 0: No, they got shopping bags.
Speaker 0: They're all excited.
Speaker 0: He said, you go on that side, stay on that side.
Speaker 0: State's going to stay on that side.
Speaker 0: But State's gone.
Speaker 0: That was the business.
Speaker 0: Every business should be calling the mayor's office.
Speaker 0: And saying stuff to the DA.
Speaker 0: She doesn't care.
Speaker 0: No, she doesn't.
Speaker 0: Look at this girl.
Speaker 0: All the shopping bags and her friends.
Speaker 0: No stores are open.
Speaker 0: Walking down the street with all the shopping bags.
Speaker 0: Yeah, I hope you get into an accident.
Speaker 0: Hope undoubtedly broke into a store up the street.
Speaker 0: Filled with stuff.
Speaker 0: What are we protesting, yeah?
Speaker 0: Looks like they hit the Adidas store, huh?
Speaker 0: Haven't heard that one in a while on dogs.
Speaker 0: Maybe this worked.
Speaker 0: Nobody in the hood got shot tonight.
Speaker 0: They got the liquor store.
Speaker 0: His arm's all bleeding.
Speaker 0: Hope it was worth it.
Speaker 0: How y'all doing today?
Speaker 0: Getting tired.
Speaker 0: Shaki Allah.
Speaker 0: They just, they just... Fucked up two cruises.
Speaker 0: Exit up.
Speaker 0: Which is up that way.
Speaker 0: I don't know who, who, who, who.
Speaker 0: Drive safe, no wheelies.
Speaker 0: Eat it.
Speaker 0: Stop playing.
Speaker 0: Shh.
Speaker 0: Yeah, they are smashing behind here.
Speaker 0: Oh, I thought it was over here.
Speaker 0: Oh, okay.
Speaker 0: They're looking down there.
Speaker 0: I got my fucking earpiece in here.
Speaker 0: What?
Speaker 0: Yeah, yeah.
Speaker 0: Call for one.
Speaker 0: Might have just made my night if... Huh?
Speaker 0: That would have made my night if that transpired like I thought it would.
Speaker 0: Yes.
Speaker 0: The aquarium.
Speaker 0: Oh, fuck.
Speaker 0: Jesus.
Speaker 0: I can't swim.
Speaker 0: Call the scuba team.
Speaker 0: We're letting them do it.
Speaker 0: I hope I wake up tomorrow and I can get out of my bag.
Speaker 0: I'm ending school making camp at my house tomorrow.
Speaker 0: It's my decision I'm making tonight.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: No, they were just fucking going to break into a store across the street, so... Nobody seems to care.
Speaker 0: What's the bike lane?
Speaker 0: We're not going to the aquarium for operation.
Speaker 0: Free the fishes.
Speaker 0: I don't know what day it is anymore.
Speaker 0: It's about now, right?
Speaker 0: I'm stoked.
Speaker 0: Oh, my God.
Speaker 0: Yes.
Speaker 0: Are we smelling that shit for the rest of my life?
Speaker 0: In the eighties.
Speaker 0: I thought that was us.
Speaker 0: No.
Speaker 0: Who the fuck drove that?
Speaker 0: It's very messy.
Speaker 0: Hey, I'm sorry.
Speaker 0: That's how it worked in the proper tunes.
Speaker 0: I thought we were going to be like going in there and... Oh, that was totally disorganized.
Speaker 0: That's the worst.
Speaker 0: Be prepared to go to Victory Road for more training.
Speaker 0: I missed the mounted unit.
Speaker 0: I'm surprised.
Speaker 0: I know we all do our best to get out of that EDT training.
Speaker 0: More people?
Speaker 0: Like, in the comments?
Speaker 0: Man, that was crazy.
Speaker 0: You can unmask him.
Speaker 0: Fucking job, Boston.
Speaker 0: Huh?
Speaker 0: Jackie, you need anything in the cruiser?
Speaker 0: I think he locked it, though.
Speaker 0: Sorry, guys.
Speaker 0: It's fucking absolute shit.
Speaker 0: Good for you, Mike.
Speaker 0: Hey, what's up?
Speaker 0: John, I thought you was driving.
Speaker 0: You drove a bit.
Speaker 0: John.
Speaker 0: What's up?
Speaker 0: Did you have a card?
Speaker 0: Huh?
Speaker 0: Did you have a card on you?
Speaker 0: No, another guy, Mike Ford, was driving it.
Speaker 0: Oh.
Speaker 0: I just wanted to make sure it wasn't broken into.
Speaker 0: That van right there?
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Good job, son.
Speaker 0: What's up, guys?
Speaker 0: What's up, Jack?
Speaker 0: I think he broke my knuckle.
Speaker 0: You're kidding me.
Speaker 0: No.
Speaker 0: Go get a look at it.
Speaker 0: Later on.
Speaker 0: Too much stuff going on.
Speaker 0: Too much fun.
Speaker 0: Maybe it's the aquarium match.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Come on, Ollie.
Speaker 0: Did you not snag that at all?
Speaker 0: I'm bad, man.
Speaker 0: It's a rematch.
Speaker 0: You know, with Joe Joe, probably the stupidest I can ever think of, that's probably the first thing Cesar did.
Speaker 0: that left me.
Speaker 0: He drove in his car and left me behind.
Speaker 0: The first thing he did was go home.
Speaker 0: he go.
Speaker 0: I called him.
Speaker 0: I tried calling him like three times.
Speaker 0: but it just doesn't, like.
Speaker 0: Wouldn't surprise me.
Speaker 0: It's not that he doesn't have one.
Speaker 0: Oh, yeah.
Speaker 0: He doesn't have one.
Speaker 0: I'm very disappointed.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: I don't have my gas mask.
Speaker 0: It's in the van.
Speaker 0: Huh?
Speaker 0: It's in the van, right?
Speaker 0: Oh yeah.
Speaker 0: Is that all right?
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: I'm totally fine.
Speaker 0: Do you want some water?
Speaker 0: Nope.
Speaker 0: I need to take a leak though.
Speaker 0: I need to take a leak.
Speaker 0: What are all these people doing?
Speaker 0: Shopping.
Speaker 0: Huh?
Speaker 0: Oh can you?
Speaker 0: I don't know.
Speaker 0: I said can we?
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: It is.
Speaker 0: The captain told us to, right?
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: It was Jackson Place, right there.
Speaker 0: I was trying to dump out every water bottle because all they're gonna do is pick it up and throw it again.
Speaker 0: I think they locked it.
Speaker 0: Yeah, it's locked.
Speaker 0: What do you think about it right here?
Speaker 0: Yeah, I think that's probably the best one just locked here.
Speaker 0: They gave us a code at one point.
Speaker 0: This used to be open.
Speaker 0: Let's take a walk and hit that.
Speaker 0: It's probably locked up.
Speaker 0: It's probably everywhere.
Speaker 0: There's another camera there.
Speaker 0: I'll hold it for now, fuck it, whatever.
Speaker 0: I want it to go when we're going down West Street with the big parking lots there next to Fajitas and Ritas.
Speaker 0: Oh, he can't let us in, right?
Speaker 0: He can't let anybody go behind, guys?
Speaker 0: Yes, sir, how you doing?
Speaker 0: Mind if we use your restroom?
Speaker 0: Not a problem, yeah, we appreciate it, thank you.
Speaker 0: Is there money for you to use the restroom?
Speaker 0: Yes, sir.
Speaker 0: All right, thank you, appreciate it.
Speaker 0: Not a problem.
Speaker 0: Is that the recline room?
Speaker 0: Yeah, yeah, I'm sorry, yeah, I'm the recline window.
Speaker 0: Oh, okay.
Speaker 0: No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Speaker 0: Guys, where's the restroom?
Speaker 0: Restroom?
Speaker 0: Yeah, men's room.
Speaker 0: Security gets you in.
Speaker 0: Where's the bathroom?
Speaker 0: Sorry, I'm sorry.
Speaker 0: Do you have the keys?
Speaker 0: No, over there.
Speaker 0: You have the keys?
Speaker 0: Follow him, follow him.
Speaker 0: Come on, man.
Speaker 0: I don't feel much of this.
Speaker 0: Just a single room, sir.
Speaker 0: Oh, no, okay.
Speaker 0: You can share.
Speaker 0: Make sure you wash your hands first.
Speaker 0: You tell me.
Speaker 0: Are we all up your step?
Speaker 0: Don't touch it, there's blood all over it.
Speaker 0: Thanks.
Speaker 0: That yours, is it?
Speaker 0: Thanks, man.
Speaker 0: All set.
Speaker 0: Yeah, I forgot to shut off my camera.
Speaker 0: I'm not washing my fucking pepper spray off.
Speaker 0: Huh?
Speaker 0: I'm not washing my pepper spray off yet.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Oh, I took this big thing off my chest.
Speaker 0: I got a jet, broke this.
Speaker 0: One of those hose things that they have in front of the stores, big brass thing.
Speaker 0: Yeah, I got one of those hooked up, man.
Speaker 0: Bricks, you got any bricks?
Speaker 0: Yeah, oh yeah.
Speaker 0: That's what hit me here.
Speaker 0: You all right, dude?
Speaker 0: You should probably get that.
Speaker 0: Oh, I don't know.
Speaker 0: I never broke a bone, so I don't know how it feels.
Speaker 0: You like, mended it?
Speaker 0: Yeah, yeah.
Speaker 0: I think it's, my knuckle's a little messed up.
Speaker 0: Huh?
Speaker 0: It's probably not broke.
Speaker 0: It's probably fucked all over.
Speaker 0: It's gonna take a while.
Speaker 0: Yeah, but I'm not taking this thing off until I'm, my toe over, man.
Speaker 0: It's gonna bleed it.
Speaker 0: Huh?
Speaker 0: It'll probably bleed everywhere.
Speaker 0: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Speaker 0: We're good.
Speaker 0: Can't leave you guys alone.
Speaker 0: Can't abandon my people.
Speaker 0: We haven't locked anybody up, man.
Speaker 0: It's just ridiculous.
Speaker 0: I'm embarrassed.
Speaker 0: Embarrassed.
Speaker 0: Most embarrassing day as a police officer.
Speaker 0: Yo, I'm sorry, guys.
Speaker 0: I gotta deal with that bullshit, man.
Speaker 0: We ain't, it ain't about George Floyd.
Speaker 0: No, it's not.
Speaker 0: No.
Speaker 0: It was until people started doing all this bullshit.
Speaker 0: Good protesters are with their message.
Speaker 0: We share the same sentiment.
Speaker 0: We do not like what happened.
Speaker 0: But Luton, Antifa, and Luton, and all that crap that's going on, what's that do?
Speaker 0: It destroys your message.
Speaker 0: Because now the average American's going, this ain't about that guy.
Speaker 0: That happened in Minnesota, Minneapolis.
Speaker 0: What's that got to do with Boston?
Speaker 0: My city, my town.
Speaker 0: I was born and raised here.
Speaker 0: This is the most embarrassing day in my career, at twenty-five years.
Speaker 0: And it's crazy because, like, I can say this because I'm black.
Speaker 0: It's like, niggas talk about fuck five-o, fuck the police, and all that other shit, but when something happens, you guys are the first people they call.
Speaker 0: You know what I mean?
Speaker 0: Like, me and my guy, like, we was dealing with a person just like us, just out and out for no reason, trying to fight.
Speaker 0: When we walked up to him, I'm like, yo, what the hell?
Speaker 0: What are you trying to prove?
Speaker 0: There's no message in that.
Speaker 0: And then, when we got in his face, he wanted to back off, and then talk about, oh, you know what, fuck you, guy, you and the police, and y'all with them niggas.
Speaker 0: I'm like, I'm a security guard.
Speaker 0: I was smoking a cigarette.
Speaker 0: So, I feel for you guys, man.
Speaker 0: I really appreciate it, man, thanks.
Speaker 0: Just like you guys see my last game.
Speaker 0: God bless, man.
Speaker 0: Be safe.
Speaker 0: What's up?
Speaker 0: I'm walking down Winter, towards the van.
Speaker 0: Do one of these things, dude.
Speaker 0: Except the fucking grass.
Speaker 0: Yeah, maybe right in here.
Speaker 0: So, yeah, I got hit with one of those, and I didn't know what the hell it was.
Speaker 0: I didn't move, and then it hit me.
Speaker 0: It hit me, and it dropped on the ground.
Speaker 0: I picked it up, and I was like.
Speaker 0: Yeah, you let it happen.
Speaker 0: Should we shut her off now?