Speaker 0: [ title  beep  ]  #  Hey,  that's  my  phone!
Speaker 0: #  Hey,  that's  my  phone  #  Let's  all  video  #  Let's  all  video  #  Let's  all  video  #  Hey,  that's  my  phone  #  That's  my  phone  #  That's  my  phone  #  Let's  all  video  [ music  playing  ]  Hands  up,  don't  shoot!
Speaker 0: Hands  up,  don't  shoot!
Speaker 0: Don't  shoot!
Speaker 0: My  hands  is  up,  don't  shoot!
Speaker 0: My  hands  is  up!
Speaker 0: We  are  holding  for  Mountain  Temple.
Speaker 0: We  are  holding  for  Mountain  Temple  with  a  group.
Speaker 0: Any  trains  over?
Speaker 0: One  block  off.
Speaker 0: Guys.
Speaker 0: Feeling  radio?
Speaker 0: Back  over  here.
Speaker 0: It's  so  hard  to  fucking  talk.
Speaker 0: What  do  you  think  your  wife  is  doing  right  now?
Speaker 0: It's  so  hard  to  have  a  fucking  concert.
Speaker 0: No,  they're  standing  for  oppression,  racism.
Speaker 0: That's  what  they're  fucking  saying.
Speaker 0: When's  the  last  time  these  three  stopped  crying?
Speaker 0: Fucking  never.
Speaker 0: There  you  go.
Speaker 0: You  got  a  nice  picture.
Speaker 0: Wow.
Speaker 0: 417,  you  probably  haven't  showered  in  a  week.
Speaker 0: You  smell  like  shit.
Speaker 0: Officer  Duffer.
Speaker 0: You're  not  going  to  be  behind  any  officers.
Speaker 0: Back  up  over  there.
Speaker 0: Can  you  keep  moving?
Speaker 0: Keep  going.
Speaker 0: Black  lives  matter!
Speaker 0: Black  lives  matter.
Speaker 0: Hey,  back  off!
Speaker 0: Back  off!
Speaker 0: [Beep,  beep]  [Indistinct  chatter]  Alright,  switch  him  up  with  this  kid  over  here.
Speaker 0: [Indistinct  chatter]  You  know  that,  right?
Speaker 0: You  know  that,  right?
Speaker 0: You  know  that  the  slave  owners...  Yeah,  get  him  out  of  here.
Speaker 0: Get  him  the  fuck  out  of  here.
Speaker 0: He  assaulted  an  officer,  sir.
Speaker 0: He  said  he...  No,  sir,  he...  That  officer,  he  assaulted  my  friend.
Speaker 0: And  the  other  officers  pulled  him  back.
Speaker 0: The  other  officers  pulled  him  back.
Speaker 0: He's  on  video.
Speaker 0: I  want  to  complain  against  that  officer.
Speaker 0: [Indistinct  chatter]  We  had  to  get  a  color  guy  over  here.
Speaker 0: [Indistinct  chatter]  We  asked  for  it.
Speaker 0: You  got  swapped  out.
Speaker 0: You  know  you're  the  token  color  guy,  right?
Speaker 0: They  just  put  you  here  to...  They  put  you  here  to  calm  the  situation.
Speaker 0: To  calm  the  situation.
Speaker 0: For  real,  I  feel  bad.
Speaker 0: I  respect  your  job.
Speaker 0: I  respect  what  you  do.
Speaker 0: I  don't  respect  that  they  don't  respect  you.
Speaker 0: They  don't  respect  you.
Speaker 0: That's  why  they  put  you  here.
Speaker 0: At  all.
Speaker 0: They're  working  for  a  place  that  doesn't  respect  you.
Speaker 0: They  don't  respect  you.
Speaker 0: We're  protesting  for  you.
Speaker 0: You're  black.
Speaker 0: For  you.
Speaker 0: We're  all  people.
Speaker 0: You're  a  minority.
Speaker 0: We  are  both  light  skinned.
Speaker 0: We  are  both  half  black.
Speaker 0: Or  whatever  you  are.
Speaker 0: But  we  are  both  men.
Speaker 0: We  are  protesting  for  you.
Speaker 0: I'm  out  here  for  you.
Speaker 0: I'm  asking  for  a  question  and  for  help.
Speaker 0: And  you  can  take  a  deep  breath.
Speaker 0: Don't  make  sense.
Speaker 0: [Indistinct  chatter]  There's  got  to  be  at  least...  How  many  deserations?
Speaker 0: Deserations?
Speaker 0: There  is.
Speaker 0: [Indistinct  chatter]  1,  2,  3,  4,  5.
Speaker 0: White  people  won't  vote.
Speaker 0: 1,  2,  3.
Speaker 0: [Indistinct  chatter]  It's  not  going  to  change.
Speaker 0: [Indistinct  chatter]  [Indistinct  chatter]  Woo!
Speaker 0: [Indistinct  chatter]  I  hope  that  they  start  showing  you  some  respect  in  your  department.
Speaker 0: [Indistinct  chatter]  These  homies  got  bags  on  their  sides.
Speaker 0: They  ready  for  it.
Speaker 0: They  ready  to  fuck  us  up.
Speaker 0: They  wanted  to.
Speaker 0: What's  in  the  bag,  sir?
Speaker 0: What's  in  the  bag?
Speaker 0: Can  you  tell  me  what's  in  that  bag?
Speaker 0: Sorry?
Speaker 0: You're  allowed  to  tell  me  what's  in  that  bag  since  we  pay  your  bills?
Speaker 0: The  people  of  Boston  pay  your  bills,  correct?
Speaker 0: With  our  tax  money?
Speaker 0: So  would  you  be  able  to  tell  me  what's  in  that  bag?
Speaker 0: No?
Speaker 0: Not  at  all.
Speaker 0: You're  not  going  to  tell  me  what's  in  the  bag?
Speaker 0: Me  too.
Speaker 0: What  is  it,  tear  gas?
Speaker 0: You  ready  for  it?
Speaker 0: Yes,  sir.
Speaker 0: Oh,  this  one's  ready  for  it.
Speaker 0: She's  getting  excited.
Speaker 0: I  just  studied  for  a  while  because  I  was  looking  for  shit.
Speaker 0: That's  1 -4 -0 -3 -1.
Speaker 0: Yes,  sir.
Speaker 0: That's  4 -0 -3 -8  on  his  ass.
Speaker 0: [Indistinct  chatter]  Six  months  of  training.
Speaker 0: Six  months.
Speaker 0: Yeah,  now  he's  looking  a  little  excited.
Speaker 0: 12  years  to  be  able  to  take  a  life.
Speaker 0: Have  a  good  night,  sir.
Speaker 0: Hey,  you!
Speaker 0: [Indistinct  chatter]  [Whistle  blows]  [Indistinct  chatter]  Six  months?
Speaker 0: [Indistinct  chatter]  [Indistinct  chatter]  [Indistinct  chatter]  [Indistinct  chatter]  [Indistinct  chatter]  [Indistinct  chatter]  [Indistinct  chatter]  [Indistinct  chatter]  Don't  fucking  throw  shit.
Speaker 0: [Indistinct  chatter]  You're  hitting  your  own  people,  man.
Speaker 0: I'm  telling  you,  I'm  getting  him  swinging.
Speaker 0: I'm  telling  you,  I'm  telling  you,  I'm  free  meditating  on  you.
Speaker 0: Free  meditating,  man.
Speaker 0: You!
Speaker 0: I  know,  bro!
Speaker 0: I'm  skating!
Speaker 0: Ladies,  I  got  a  picture.
Speaker 0: Can  I  get  a  picture?
Speaker 0: Can  I  use  your  sign?
Speaker 0: Can  I  get  one  with  you?
Speaker 0: Can  you  take  one  with  me?
Speaker 0: You  good?
Speaker 0: Let's  go.
Speaker 0: Yeah.
Speaker 0: Start  my  camera.
Speaker 0: One.
Speaker 0: Take  a  knee!
Speaker 0: A  plethora  of  officers  of  Boston,  Massachusetts,  refusing  to  take  a  knee.
Speaker 0: Even  a  fellow  black  officer  refusing  to  take  a  knee.
Speaker 0: Refusing  to  take  a  knee?
Speaker 0: Black  lives  matter.
Speaker 0: Who  are  you?
Speaker 0: That's  true.
Speaker 0: Black  lives  matter.
Speaker 0: Your  life  matters.
Speaker 0: And  you  still  refuse  to  take  a  knee.
Speaker 0: We're  all  down  here.
Speaker 0: No  white  shit!
Speaker 0: Black  lives  matter!
Speaker 0: We're  gonna  play  some  old  football  games  over  a  kneel,  but  all  of  a  sudden  it's  okay,  right?
Speaker 0: The  fuck?
Speaker 0: Fuck  y 'all  kneeling?
Speaker 0: Not  y 'all.
Speaker 0: Y 'all  good.
Speaker 0: But  they  don't  give  a  fuck.
Speaker 0: Why  we  kneeling?
Speaker 0: We've  been  kneeling  for  months.
Speaker 0: Months.
Speaker 0: Nothing.
Speaker 0: They  kneeled  on  my  neck.
Speaker 0: Not  my  neck,  but  you  know.
Speaker 0: They'll  kneel  on  your  neck,  but  you  won't  kneel  for  tolerance.
Speaker 0: For  real.
Speaker 0: They'll  kneel  on  your  neck,  but  they  won't  kneel  for  tolerance.
Speaker 0: Kneel  on  our  neck,  but  no  kneel  for  tolerance?
Speaker 0: They'll  kneel  on  our  neck,  but  you  won't  kneel  for  tolerance.
Speaker 0: It  mean  nothing.
Speaker 0: I'm  gonna  kneel  right  now,  and  they're  gonna  kill  me  tomorrow.
Speaker 0: You  gonna  kneel  again?
Speaker 0: I  die  tomorrow.
Speaker 0: George  Floyd!
Speaker 0: Can  I  ask  y 'all  a  question?
Speaker 0: Do  y 'all  care  about  what's  going  on  with  him?
Speaker 0: Watch  his  body  language.
Speaker 0: Don't  even  look.
Speaker 0: He's  gonna  give  a  fuck -loss.
Speaker 0: Do  you  care  about  what's  going  on,  man?
Speaker 0: Obviously  not.
Speaker 0: Black  police  showing  up  with  a  white  cop.
Speaker 0: It's  a  head  nod,  a  yes  or  no.
Speaker 0: [indistinct  shouting]  [indistinct  shouting]  Do  you  care  about  what's  going  on?
Speaker 0: It's  fucking  crazy.
Speaker 0: I  asked  every  fucking  cop  down  this  county.
Speaker 0: You're  the  only  one  that  answered.
Speaker 0: You  fucked  with  all  that's  going  on,  and  he  said,  "Yes,
Speaker 0: sir."
Speaker 0: None  of  them  motherfuckers  answered.
Speaker 0: None  of  the  police  officers  answered.
Speaker 0: They  didn't  care  the  fuck  what  was  going  on.
Speaker 0: But  this  police  officer  said  he  truly  cares  what's  going  on  here.
Speaker 0: Respect  to  this  officer  who  cares  about  what's  going  on  here.
Speaker 0: Nobody  got  a  tooth  right  now.
Speaker 0: Y 'all  got  so  much  to  say.
Speaker 0: Ain't  nobody  got  a  tooth.
Speaker 0: I  just  want  to  know,  do  you  have  a  collarbone  yet?
Speaker 0: Yes,  but  they  can't  answer  nothing.
Speaker 0: They  can't  answer  nothing.
Speaker 0: [indistinct  shouting]  What  are  you  doing  right  now?
Speaker 0: [indistinct  shouting]  The  fucking  street  is  getting  so  confusing  with  the  fucking  sand.
Speaker 0: [indistinct  shouting]  [indistinct  shouting]  [indistinct  shouting]  [indistinct  shouting]  [indistinct  shouting]  Yes.
Speaker 0: Yes.
Speaker 0: Hold  on,  hold  on.
Speaker 0: Hold  on,  Charco.
Speaker 0: All  right.
Speaker 0: Now  he's  not  going  to  answer  because  he's  going  to  take  now.
Speaker 0: No,  no,  sir.
Speaker 0: That's  an  okay  question.
Speaker 0: That's  how  I  take  it.
Speaker 0: Hey,  hey,  if  one  of  these  cops  right  here  was  knocking  my  head  off,  would  you  speak  up?
Speaker 0: Not  out  here,  you  won't.
Speaker 0: No.
Speaker 0: None  of  them.
Speaker 0: I  swear  to  you.
Speaker 0: Come  on,  bro.
Speaker 0: Bro,  listen.
Speaker 0: I  gained  most  of  my  knowledge  from  my  granduncle,  bro.
Speaker 0: Not  my  rightful  uncle,  my  granduncle,  bro.
Speaker 0: You  understand  what  I'm  saying?
Speaker 0: They  will  not  speak  up  out  here.
Speaker 0: What's  their  name?
Speaker 0: They're  all  your  partners.
Speaker 0: I  swear  to  you  now.
Speaker 0: And  they're  supposed  to  tell  you  their  name  and  badge.
Speaker 0: They're  supposed  to  say  names  and  badges.
Speaker 0: That's  the  law.
Speaker 0: Right  there.
Speaker 0: So,  I  mean,  I  can  report.
Speaker 0: You're  good.
Speaker 0: I  can  report  you.
Speaker 0: I  can't  even  see  your  badge.
Speaker 0: So,  that's  good.
Speaker 0: But  you.
Speaker 0: What's  your  name?
Speaker 0: All  right,  because  I  can  report  you.
Speaker 0: I  can  report  you.
Speaker 0: Oh,  they're  bugging.
Speaker 0: They're  bugging.
Speaker 0: No,  they're  bugging.
Speaker 0: No,  what  the  fuck?
Speaker 0: Yo,  listen  to  me.
Speaker 0: Listen  to  me.
Speaker 0: But  if  they  do  that  shit,  don't  hit  us.
Speaker 0: Don't  be  a  big  mistake.
Speaker 0: I  got,  like,  three,  four  of  them.
Speaker 0: Wait  a  minute.
Speaker 0: No,  no,  seriously.
Speaker 0: Just  a  second.
Speaker 0: No,  no,  no,  listen.
Speaker 0: I  know  this  talent.
Speaker 0: This  ain't  new.
Speaker 0: I  know  this.
Speaker 0: And  I  appreciate  that.
Speaker 0: I  appreciate  that.
Speaker 0: Switch  with  me.
Speaker 0: You  good?
Speaker 0: You  all  right?
Speaker 0: Yo,  listen  to  me.
Speaker 0: I 'll  bring  you  back  for  this.
Speaker 0: I  swear  to  God  I  will.
Speaker 0: I'll  bring  you  back  for  this.
Speaker 0: [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinguishable  talking]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]  [indistinct  chatter]